<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author?, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- If you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - read /hooks/README! -->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>673</id>
		<date>2010-05-26</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.6-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.8-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4222</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1455</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the DOCSIS (Data Over Cable Service Interface Specifications) dissector and can be exploited to e.g. cause a crash via specially crafted DOCSIS traffic.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>672</id>
		<date>2010-05-22</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-captcha</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_3.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_3.3-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4220</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/803566.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the CAPTCHA module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Certain input passed via the CAPTCHA description is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation requires "administer CAPTCHA settings" permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>671</id>
		<date>2010-05-17</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-filefield</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_3.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_3.3-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4207</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/791050.</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in the FileField module for Drupal, which potentially can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The security issue exists due to improper creation of a default extension for a new file field when the field configuration page is not saved and can be exploited to upload arbitrary files to a directory inside the webroot.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary PHP code but requires "create" or "edit" permission for the file field.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>670</id>
		<date>2010-05-17</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-imagefield</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_3.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_3.3-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4208</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/791054</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in the ImageField module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose potentially sensitive information.
			The security issue exists due to improper access permission checks for thumbnails of restricted images when the Private Downloads setting is used and can be exploited to view the thumbnail.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>669</id>
		<date>2010-05-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>gnustep-base</package>
		<vulnerable>1.18.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.18.0-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4210</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1457
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1620</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in GNUStep Base, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to potentially gain escalated privileges or disclose sensitive information.
			1) The "gdomap" application includes the content of files in error messages when parsing a configuration file specified via the "-c" command line option. This can be exploited to disclose sensitive information by passing an arbitrary file as configuration file to the application.
			2) An integer overflow error exists in the "gdomap" application when parsing configuration files. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow when a specially crafted configuration file containing a large number lines is being processed.
			Successful exploitation of the vulnerabilities requires that the "gdomap" binary has the "setuid" bit set and is owned by e.g. root.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>668</id>
		<date>2010-04-27</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.32-4locris1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.32-4locris2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4183</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1148
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0727
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1162</cve>
		<desc>Three vulnerabilities have been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) A vulnerability is caused due to a NULL-pointer dereference error within the "cifs_create()" function in fs/cifs/dir.c. This can be exploited to cause a crash when a file without an associated "nameidata" structure is created.
			2) There was a check for mandatory locking where the GFS/GFS2 locking code skipped the lock in case sgid bits are set for the file. This can be triggered to cause a crash on a system mounting a GFS/GFS2 filesystem.
			3) The vulnerability is caused due to a memory leak within the "release_one_tty()" function in drivers/char/tty_io.c, which can be exploited to e.g. cause a DoS due to memory exhaustion.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>667</id>
		<date>2010-04-27</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>fetchmail</package>
		<vulnerable>6.3.13-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.3.16-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4195</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1167</cve>
		<desc>Fetchmail did not properly sanitize external input (mail headers and UID). When a multi-character locale (such as UTF-8) was in use, this could cause memory exhaustion and thus a denial of service, because fetchmail's report.c functions assumed that non-success of [v]snprintf was due to insufficient buffer size allocation. It would then repeatedly reallocate a larger buffer and fail formatting again.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>666</id>
		<date>2010-04-26</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>cacti</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.7e-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.7e-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4193</bts>
		<cve>No CVE yet, see http://seclists.org/fulldisclosure/2010/Apr/272.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Cacti, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct SQL injection attacks.
			Input passed via the "export_item_id" parameter to templates_export.php is not properly sanitised before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code.
			Successful exploitation requires that the attacker is allowed to export templates.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>665</id>
		<date>2010-04-25</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>nano</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.9-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.9-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4196</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1160
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1161</cve>
		<desc>Some security issues have been reported in GNU nano, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to perform certain actions with escalated privileges.
			1) The application does not properly verify if the file currently being edited has been changed outside the context of the current editing session before writing to it, which can be exploited to e.g. overwrite arbitrary files via symlink attacks.
			2) A race condition exists when creating backup files, which can be exploited to take the ownership of arbitrary files via e.g. symlink attacks.
			Successful exploitation requires that the victim is tricked into editing files owned by the attacker and that the backup functionality is enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>664</id>
		<date>2010-04-24</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>polkit</package>
		<vulnerable>0.96-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.96-3locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4199</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0750</cve>
		<desc>A weakness has been reported in PolicyKit, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose certain system information.
			The weakness is caused due to the "pkexec" utility returning different results depending on the existence of files, which can be exploited to e.g. determine if a file exists in a restricted directory.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>663</id>
		<date>2010-04-23</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>memcached</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.5-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4182</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1152</cve>
		<desc>A weakness has been reported in memcached, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to potentially cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The weakness is caused due to the application improperly handling received TCP data. This can be exploited to consume large amounts of memory and temporarily hang or potentially crash an affected server by sending an overly large number of bytes without a terminating newline ('\n') character to TCP port 11211.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>662</id>
		<date>2010-04-22</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>glibc</package>
		<vulnerable>2.11.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.11.1-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4166</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0296
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0830</cve>
		<desc>Dan Rosenberg reported two security issues in glibc:
			1) "ncpmount" and "mount.cifs" failed to properly sanitize provided mountpoint directory names (specifically, special characters such as newlines were not stripped). An attacker could create a directory with newline characters in its name and issue an ncpmount / mount.cifs command to mount to that directory, allowing them to corrupt /etc/mtab and potentially add unauthorized mounting options for other devices.
			2) A memory corruption vulnerability in ld.so: When processing maliciously crafted ELF binaries using ld.so, regardless of whether execution of those binaries is intended (for example, using the "--verify" flag, which should not lead to any code execution), arbitrary code execution can be achieved.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>661</id>
		<date>2010-04-21</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>j2sdk</package>
		<vulnerable>6-22locris1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6-23locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4189</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0886
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0887
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1423</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in Sun Java, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an input sanitation error in the Java Deployment Toolkit browser plugin. This can be exploited to pass arbitrary arguments to javaw.exe and e.g. execute a JAR file placed on a network share in a privileged context.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code by tricking a user into visiting a malicious web page.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>660</id>
		<date>2010-04-16</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>sudo</package>
		<vulnerable>1.7.2-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.7.2-4locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4188</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1163</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in sudo, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused due to an error within the command matching functionality, which can be exploited to run a "sudoedit" executable within the current working directory.
			Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges, but requires that the attacker is allowed to use sudo's "sudoedit" pseudo-command, that the PATH environment variable contains "." while the directories do not contain any other "sudoedit" executable, and that the "ignore_dot" or "secure_path" options are disabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>659</id>
		<date>2010-04-14</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>kdebase-workspace</package>
		<vulnerable>4.3.5-7</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.3.5-8locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4129</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0436</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in KDE, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused due to a race condition within KDM when creating the control socket during a user login. This can be exploited to change the access permissions of arbitrary files to world-writable, which can be leveraged to e.g. execute arbitrary code with escalated privileges.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>658</id>
		<date>2010-04-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mediawiki</package>
		<vulnerable>1.15.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.15.1-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4184</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1150</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in MediaWiki, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct cross-site request forgery attacks.
			The application allows users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any validity checks to verify the requests. This can be exploited to e.g. force a victim into executing malicious javascript.
			Successful exploitation requires "$wgAllowUserJs" to be set to "true" in LocalSettings.php.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>657</id>
		<date>2010-04-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>tetex</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0-18</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0-19locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4153</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0739</cve>
		<desc>Marc Schoenefeld found an integer overflow in the way    
			TeX text formatting system processed special commands.   
			If a user was tricked into processing a specially-crafted
			typesetter-independent .dvi (DeVice Independent) file,
			it could lead to dvips executable crash or, potentially,   
			to arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the user
			running dvips.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>656</id>
		<date>2010-04-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-views</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_2.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_2.10-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4179</bts>
		<cve>No CVE reference, see http://drupal.org/node/765022.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Views module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being used to import views. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code.
			Successful exploitation requires "administer views" permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>655</id>
		<date>2010-04-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal-views</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_1.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_1.7-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4178</bts>
		<cve>No CVE reference, see http://drupal.org/node/765022.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Views module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being used to import views. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code.
			Successful exploitation requires "administer views" permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>654</id>
		<date>2010-04-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-i18n</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_1.3-1locris1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_1.4-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4134</bts>
		<cve>No CVE reference, see http://drupal.org/node/764998.</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in the Internationalization module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			1) Certain input passed to translating blocks is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			2) Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation requires "translate interface" or "administer blocks" permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>653</id>
		<date>2010-04-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.32-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.32-4locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4175</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1146</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the ReiserFS file system implementation not properly restricting access to the ".reiserfs_priv" directory, which can be exploited to e.g. gain root privileges by modifying ACLs or extended attributes.
			Successful exploitation requires that the ReiserFS file system is used.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>652</id>
		<date>2010-04-03</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>3.6.2-1locris1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.6.3-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4171</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1121</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a use-after-free error when moving DOM nodes between documents and can be exploited via a specially crafted web page.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>651</id>
		<date>2010-04-02</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>j2sdk</package>
		<vulnerable>6-21</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6-22locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4167</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3555
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0082
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0084
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0085
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0087
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0088
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0089
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0090
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0091
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0092
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0093
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0094
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0095
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0837
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0838
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0839
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0840
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0841
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0842
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0843
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0844
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0845
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0846
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0847
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0848
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0849
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0850</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in Sun Java, where some have an unknown impact and others can be exploited by malicious people to manipulate certain data, disclose potentially sensitive information, cause a DoS (Denial of Service), or compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) An error in the implementation of the "HeadspaceSoundbank" class can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow via a crafted Soundbank file with an overly long name.
			2) An error in the implementation of the "HeadspaceSoundbank" class can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a crafted Soundbank file with an overly long record.
			3) An input validation error in the processing of image files can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow, e.g. if a user visits a web page containing a specially crafted java applet.
			Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities allows execution of arbitrary code.
			4) Unspecified vulnerabilities exist in the ImageIO, Java 2D, Java Runtime Environment, Java Web Start, Java Plug-in, Pack200, Sound, and HotSpot Server components.
			5) An error in the JSSE component while handling TLS session re-negotiations can be exploited to manipulate certain data.
			5) An unspecified error in the Java Web Start, Java Plug-in component can be exploited to manipulate certain data or cause a DoS.
			6) Two unspecified errors in the Java Runtime Environment can be exploited to disclose unspecified information.
			7) An unspecified error in the Java Web Start, Java Plug-in component can be exploited to cause a DoS.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>650</id>
		<date>2010-04-01</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>php</package>
		<vulnerable>5.3.1-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.3.2-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4165</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1128
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1129
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1130
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0397</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in PHP, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) An error in the session extension can be exploited to bypass the "safe_mode" and "open_basedir" feature.
			2) A validation error exists within the "tempnam()" function, which can be exploited to bypass the "safe_mode" feature.
			A NULL pointer dereference has been reported in the xmlrpc extension, in a call to estrdup(). This bug can at least be used to perform DoS attacks.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>649</id>
		<date>2010-03-31</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>amsn</package>
		<vulnerable>0.98.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.98.1-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4161</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0744</cve>
		<desc>Gabriel Menezes Nunes has discovered a security issue in aMSN, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct spoofing attacks.
			The security issue is caused due to the application improperly verifying the validity of the SSL certificate presented when logging in. This can be exploited to spoof a valid server and obtain the user's MSN username and password via e.g. a man-in-the-middle attack. </desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>648</id>
		<date>2010-03-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>curl</package>
		<vulnerable>7.19.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>7.19.7-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4162</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0734</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in cURL / libcURL, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or compromise an application using the library.
			The security issue is caused due to an error when returning data to the registered callback function for downloading compressed content over HTTP. The library may send back up to 64Kb of data to the callback function, exceeding the documented maximum data size of 16Kb (CURL_MAX_WRITE_SIZE). This can potentially lead to buffer overflows in client applications.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>647</id>
		<date>2010-03-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>krb5</package>
		<vulnerable>1.7-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.7-5locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4137</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0628</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Kerberos, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an assertion error within the "spnego_gss_accept_sec_context()" function in src/lib/gssapi/spnego/spnego_mech.c when receiving an invalid packet, which can be exploited to e.g. crash an application using the library by sending a specially crafted packet.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>646</id>
		<date>2010-03-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>pulseaudio</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.21-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.21-3locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4130</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-1299</cve>
		<desc>This fixes a security issue, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to perform certain actions with escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused due to the application performing chown() and chmod() calls without checking for symbolic links in existing directories. This can be exploited to e.g. change permissions and ownership of arbitrary files via symlink attacks.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>645</id>
		<date>2010-03-28</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal-mimemail</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_1.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_1.1-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4159</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/751934.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Mime Mail module for Drupal, while can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the PCRE regular expression engine, which can be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code.
			Successful exploitation requires the ability to send HTML email via the Mime Mail module.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>644</id>
		<date>2010-03-23</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>3.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.6.2-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4158</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1028</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow error when processing WOFF fonts. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a web page embedding a WOFF font with an overly large "origLen" field.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>643</id>
		<date>2010-03-16</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>libesmtp</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.4-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4141</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-2408</cve>
		<desc>libesmtp did not properly handle a '\0' character in a domain name in the subject's Common Name (CN) field of an X.509 certificate, which allows man-in-the-middle attackers to spoof arbitrary SSL servers via a crafted certificate issued by a legitimate Certification Authority.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>642</id>
		<date>2010-03-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-i18n</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_1.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_1.3-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4134</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/731632.</cve>
		<desc>See FSA641 for details.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>641</id>
		<date>2010-03-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal-i18n</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_2.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_2.6-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4134</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/731632.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Internationalization module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being used to translate the text. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code by passing a malicious string to the input filter.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>640</id>
		<date>2010-03-11</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6</package>
		<vulnerable>6.15-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.16-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4133</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/731710.</cve>
		<desc>See FSA639 for details.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>639</id>
		<date>2010-03-11</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal</package>
		<vulnerable>5.21-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.22-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4132</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/731710.</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks and bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) Input passed via the "langcode", "name", and "native" parameters in the languages interface while using the Locale module is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation requires "administer languages" permissions.
			2) An error in the handling of certain sessions can be exploited to maintain an open session despite the user being blocked.
</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>638</id>
		<date>2010-03-10</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>2.9.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.9.2-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4131</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0682</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The vulnerability is caused due to WordPress not properly restricting access to trashed posts, which can be exploited to e.g. view a trashed post by accessing it's page directly.
			Successful exploitation requires a valid user account.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>637</id>
		<date>2010-03-09</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>xar</package>
		<vulnerable>1.5.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.5.2-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4128</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0055</cve>
		<desc>Braden Thomas from Apple has discovered a signature verification bypass issue in xar.  The issue is that xar_open assumes that the checksum is stored at offset 0, but xar_signature_copy_signed_data uses xar property "checksum/offset" to find the offset to the checksum when validating the signature.  As a result, a modified xar archive can pass signature validation by putting the checksum for the modified TOC at offset 0, pointing "checksum/offset" at the non-modified checksum at a higher offset, and using the original non-modified signature.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
