<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- if you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - xmllint is your friend
-->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>240</id>
		<date>2007-08-07</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>joomla</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.12-2terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.13-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2290</bts>
		<cve>No CVE for this issue, see: http://www.joomla.org/content/view/3677/1/</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Joomla!, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct session fixation attacks, cross-site scripting attacks or HTTP response splitting attacks.
			1) Certain unspecified input passed in com_search, com_content and mod_login is not properly sanitised before being returned to a user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			2) Input passed to the "url" parameter is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTTP headers, which will be included in a response sent to the user, allowing for execution of arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			3) An error exists in the handling of sessions and can be exploited to hijack another user's session by tricking the user into logging in after following a specially crafted link.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>239</id>
		<date>2007-08-07</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>libvorbis</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.0-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2293</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4029
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3106</cve>
		<desc>David Thiel has reported some vulnerabilities in libvorbis, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise an application using the library.
			1) A boundary error exists in the way the "_01inverse()" function in res.c processes "blocksize_0" and "blocksize_1" values, which can be exploited to cause a heap overwrite.
			2) A boundary error exists in the way the "vorbis_info_clear()" function in info.c processes invalid mapping types, which can be exploited to trigger a call to a value outside the dispatch table.
			3) Invalid "blocksize" values passed to the "vorbis_dsp_clear()" function in block.c result in an invalid memory access, which can be exploited to cause a DoS.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>238</id>
		<date>2007-08-07</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>clamav</package>
		<vulnerable>0.90.2-1terminus2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.90.2-1terminus3</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2257</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3725</cve>
		<desc>Metaeye SG has reported a vulnerability in ClamAV, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to a NULL-pointer dereference error within libclamav/unrar/unrarvm.c when handling RAR archives and can be exploited to cause a crash via a specially crafted RAR archive.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>237</id>
		<date>2007-08-07</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>apache</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.2.4-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2298</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5752
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1863
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3304</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been acknowledged in Apache, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) An error in the mod_status module can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			2) An error in the Multi-Processing Module (MPM) can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS.
			3) An error in the mod_cache module in the handling of Cache-Control headers can be exploited to crash the child process via specially crafted requests. This could lead to a DoS if using a threaded Multi-Processing Module.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>236</id>
		<date>2007-08-03</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>vim</package>
		<vulnerable>7.0-4terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>7.0-4terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2292</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2953</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered a vulnerability in Vim, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			A format string error in the "helptags_one()" function in src/ex_cmds.c when running the "helptags" command can be exploited to execute arbitrary code via specially crafted help files.
			Successful exploitation requires that the user is tricked into running "helptags" on malicious data.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>235</id>
		<date>2007-08-02</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.4-1terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.6-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2252
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2253
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2303</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3656
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3670
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3734
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3735
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3736
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3737
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3738
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3089
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3844</cve>
		<desc>1) Michal Zalewski has discovered a vulnerability in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information and conduct spoofing attacks.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the handling of the "wyciwyg://" URI handler. This can be exploited to access or spoof contents from a previously cached web site e.g. via HTTP 302 redirects when a user visits a malicious web page.
			2) The problem is that Firefox registers the "firefoxurl://" URI handler and allows invoking firefox with arbitrary command line arguments. Using e.g. the "-chrome" parameter it is possible to execute arbitrary Javascript in chrome context. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary commands e.g. when a user visits a malicious web site using other browsers.
			3) Various errors in the browser engine can be exploited to cause memory corruption and potentially to execute arbitrary code.
			4) Various errors in the Javascript engine can be exploited to cause memory corruption and potentially to execute arbitrary code.
			5) An error in the "addEventListener" and "setTimeout" methods can be exploited to inject script into another site's context, circumventing the browser's same-origin policy.
			6) An error in the cross-domain handling can be exploited to inject arbitrary HTML and script code in a sub-frame of another web site.
			7) An unspecified error in the handling of elements outside of documents allows an attacker to call an event handler and execute arbitrary code with chrome privileges.
			8) An unspecified error in the handling of "XPCNativeWrapper" can lead to execution of user-supplied code.
			9) The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the handling of "about:blank" pages loaded by chrome in an addon. This can be exploited to execute script code under chrome privileges by e.g. clicking on a link opened in an "about:blank" window created and populated in a certain ways by an addon.
			Successful exploitation requires that certain addons are installed.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>234</id>
		<date>2007-07-31</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>gimp</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.13-2terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.2.13-2terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2237</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4519
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2949</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Gimp, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) An integer overflow exists within the function "seek_to_and_unpack_pixeldata()" in plug-ins/common/psd.c. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by tricking a user into opening a specially crafted PSD file with large width or height values.
			2) Multiple integer overflows exist within the DICOM, PNM, PSD, PSP, Sun RAS, XBM, and XWD loader plugins. These can potentially be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by tricking a user into opening specially crafted image files.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>233</id>
		<date>2007-07-30</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>bind</package>
		<vulnerable>9.4.1-1terminus2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.4.1-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2285</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2926</cve>
		<desc>Amit Klein has reported a vulnerability in BIND, which can be exploited by malicious people to poison the DNS cache.
			The vulnerability is caused due to predictable query IDs in outgoing queries (e.g. if BIND works as resolver or when sending NOTIFYs to slaves) and can be exploited to poison the DNS cache when the query ID is guessed.
			Reportedly, the chance to guess the next query ID for 50% of the queries (if the query ID is even) is 1 to 8.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>232</id>
		<date>2007-07-29</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>libarchive</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.1-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.1-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2258</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3641
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3644
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3645</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in libarchive, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to a NULL pointer dereference, an infinite loop, and a buffer overflow when processing certain malformed pax extension headers. These can be exploited to crash an application, cause a high CPU load or potentially execute arbitrary code by tricking a user or automated system to process a specially crafted archive file with an application using the library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>231</id>
		<date>2007-07-29</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>tcpdump</package>
		<vulnerable>3.9.5-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.9.5-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2270</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3798</cve>
		<desc>mu-b has reported a vulnerability in tcpdump, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the incorrect use of the return value of "snprintf()" in print-bgp.c. This can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow by sending specially crafted BGP packets.
			Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>230</id>
		<date>2007-07-29</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>perl-net-dns</package>
		<vulnerable>0.59-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.60-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2217</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3377
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3409</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in the Net::DNS Perl module, which can be exploited to poison the DNS cache or to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) An error exists in the handling of DNS queries where IDs are incremented with a fixed value and are additionally used for child processes in a forking server. This can be exploited to poison the DNS cache of an application using the module if a valid ID is guessed.
			2) An error in the PP implementation within the "dn_expand()" function can be exploited to cause a stack overflow due to an endless loop via a specially crafted DNS packet.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>229</id>
		<date>2007-07-29</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>c-ares</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.2-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.0-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2159</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3152
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3153</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in c-ares, which can be exploited by malicious people to poison the DNS cache.
			The vulnerability is caused due to predictable DNS "Transaction ID" field in DNS queries and can be exploited to poison the DNS cache of an application using the library if a valid ID is guessed.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>228</id>
		<date>2007-07-29</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>kvirc</package>
		<vulnerable>3.2.0-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.2.5-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2214</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2951</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered a vulnerability in KVIrc, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the "parseIrcUrl()" function in src/kvirc/kernel/kvi_ircurl.cpp not properly sanitising parts of the URI when building the command for KVIrc's internal script system. This can be exploited to inject and execute commands for the KVIrc script system (including the "run" command, which can be leveraged to execute shell commands) by e.g. tricking a user into opening a malicious "irc://" (or similar URI like "irc6://") URI.
			Successful exploitation requires that KVIrc is the default handler for "irc://" or similar URIs.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>227</id>
		<date>2007-07-28</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>lighttpd</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.13-3terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.16-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2271</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3946
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3947
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3948
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3949
			ttp://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3950</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in lighttpd, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions, cause a DoS (Denial of Service), or potentially to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) An error in the processing of HTTP headers can be exploited to cause a DoS by sending duplicate HTTP headers with a trailing whitespace character.
			2) An error in mod_auth can be exploited to cause a DoS by sending requests with the algorithm set to "MD5-sess" and without a cnonce.
			3) An error when parsing Auth-Digest headers in mod_auth can potentially be exploited to cause a DoS by sending multiple whitespace characters.
			4) An error exists in the mechanism that limits the number of active connections. This can be exploited to cause a DoS.
			5) An error exists in the processing of HTTP requests. This can be exploited to access restricted files by adding a "/" to an URL.
			6) An error exists in mod_scgi. This can be exploited to cause a DoS by sending a SCGI request and closing the connection while lighttpd processes the request.
			7) The return value of "base64_decode" in mod_auth was not checked properly when parsing the credentials for basic authentication, which could lead to accessing uninitialized memory.
			8) An error in the header parsing code can lead to access of memory outside of the original boundaries and can cause a memory corruption.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can potentially be exploited to execute arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>226</id>
		<date>2007-07-26</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>j2sdk</package>
		<vulnerable>6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2255</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3716</cve>
		<desc>Brad Hill has reported a vulnerability in Sun JDK and JRE, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error when processing XSLT stylesheets contained in XSLT Transforms in XML signatures. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary code when an application processes a specially crafted XML signature.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>225</id>
		<date>2007-07-26</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>j2re</package>
		<vulnerable>6-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2254</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3655
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3716</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Sun Java Web Start, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the Java Web Start component (javaws.exe) when processing JNLP files. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted JNLP file with an overly long codebase attribute.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code e.g. when a user visits a malicious website.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>224</id>
		<date>2007-07-26</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.20-5terminus7</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.20-5terminus8</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2235</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3513
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3107</cve>
		<desc>Security issues have been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) The USBLCD driver does not limit the memory consumption during writes to the device. This can be exploited to cause an out-of-memory condition by writing a large amount of data to an affected device.
			Successful exploitation requires write access to a device using the driver.
			2) A vulnerability is caused due to an error within the "decode_choice()" function in net/netfilter/bf_conntrack_h323_asn1.c when handling choices that are still encoded in the fixed-size bitfield. This can be exploited to cause access to undefined types, resulting in a crash.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>223</id>
		<date>2007-07-23</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>joomla</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.12-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.12-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2216</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue, see http://joomlacode.org/gf/project/joomla/tracker/?action=TrackerItemEdit&amp;tracker_item_id=5654</cve>
		<desc>Cindy Chee has discovered a vulnerability in Joomla!, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Input passed to the "Title" and "Section Name" form fields when creating new sections in Section Manager is not properly sanitised before being stored. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which is executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the data is viewed.
			Successful exploitation requires that the target user has valid administrator credentials.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>222</id>
		<date>2007-07-22</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>qemu</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.0-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2011</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1320
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1321
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1322
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1323
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1366</cve>
		<desc>Tavis Ormandy has reported some vulnerabilities in QEMU, which can be exploited by malicious uses to bypass certain security restrictions or cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) A boundary error exists within the "cirrus_invalidate_region()" function of the Cirrus video driver, which can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
			2) The size of ethernet frames is not correctly checked against the "MTU" before being copied into the registers of the NE2000 network driver. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
			3) An integer signedness error when processing data in the NE2000 device registers can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
			Successful exploitation of 1) through 3) may allow the execution of arbitrary code.
			4) Errors when handling the "icebp" instruction can be exploited to cause a DoS by terminating the emulation session.
			5) An error within the handling of the "aam" instruction can result in a division by zero, which can be exploited to cause a DoS.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>221</id>
		<date>2007-07-22</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>flashplugin</package>
		<vulnerable>9.0.31.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.0.48.0-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2240</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3456
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3457
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2022</cve>
		<desc>Critical vulnerabilities have been identified in Adobe Flash Player that could allow an attacker who successfully exploits these potential vulnerabilities to take control of the affected system. A malicious SWF must be loaded in Flash Player by the user for an attacker to exploit these potential vulnerabilities.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>220</id>
		<date>2007-07-22</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>0.99.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.99.6-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2218</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3389
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3390
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3391
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3392
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3393</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			Errors exist within the DHCP/BOOTP dissector or when processing HTTP chunked responses, iSeries capture files, or DCP ETSI, SSL, or MMS packets. These can be exploited to cause a crash, excessive loops, or consume large amounts of memory when parsing a specially crafted packet that is either captured off the wire or loaded via a capture file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>219</id>
		<date>2007-07-22</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>avahi</package>
		<vulnerable>0.6.17-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.6.17-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2209</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3372</cve>
		<desc>Emanuele Aina has reported a security issue in Avahi, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The security issue is caused due to an "assert()" error when receiving empty TXT data over D-Bus for registration. This can be exploited to terminate the Avahi daemon by sending empty TXT data.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>218</id>
		<date>2007-07-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.20-5terminus6</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.20-5terminus7</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2211</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3104</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).
			The vulnerability is caused due to a NULL pointer dereference within the function "sysfs_readdir()" when handling pointers to inodes. This can be exploited to crash a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>217</id>
		<date>2007-07-09</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>xvidcore</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.3-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2212</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3329</cve>
		<desc>Trixter Jack has reported a vulnerability in the Xvid library, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an array indexing error in the "get_intra_block()" function within src/bitstream/mbcoding.c while processing Xvid Avi files. This can be exploited to corrupt memory via a specially crafted file. Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>216</id>
		<date>2007-07-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>2.1.3-1terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.2.1-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2067
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2158
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2213</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2821
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3140</cve>
		<desc>Janek Vind has discovered a vulnerability in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct SQL injection attacks. Input passed to the "cookie" parameter in wp-admin/admin-ajax.php is not properly sanitised before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code. Successful exploitation allows e.g. retrieving administrator password hashes, but requires knowledge of the database table prefix.
			A vulnerability has been discovered in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct SQL injection attacks. Input passed to the "wp.suggestCategories" method in xmlrpc.php is not properly sanitised before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code. Successful exploitation allows e.g. retrieving usernames and password hashes, but requires valid user credentials and knowledge of the database table prefix.
			Alexander Concha has discovered a vulnerability in WordPress and WordPress MU, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions and to compromise a vulnerable system. The vulnerability is caused due to improper authentication verification. This can be exploited to add the custom field "_wp_attached_file" to a post, upload a PHP script to an arbitrary path with wp-app.php or app.php, and execute arbitrary PHP code. Successful exploitation requires valid Editor credentials and that the system is configured to allow uploads.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>215</id>
		<date>2007-07-01</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openoffice.org</package>
		<vulnerable>2.1.0-6terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.1.0-6terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2196</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0245
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2754</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in OpenOffice, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) An error exists when parsing the "prdata" tag in RTF files where the first token is smaller that the second one. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted RTF files.
			2) A vulnerability is caused due to the use of a vulnerable copy of the FreeType library, which can be exploited to cause a heap based buffer overflow by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted document.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>214</id>
		<date>2007-07-01</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>clamav</package>
		<vulnerable>0.90.2-1terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.90.2-1terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2042</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2650
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3023
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3024
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3025
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3122
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3123</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in ClamAV, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) An error exists within the OLE2 parser when handling objects with malformed FAT partitions and large property sizes. This can be exploited to cause a DoS due to storage and CPU resource consumption by scanning a specially crafted OLE2 file.
			2) An error in the processing of RAR files can be exploited to crash the process via a specially crafted RAR file.
			3) A boundary error exists within the file /libclamav/unsp.c, which can be exploited to crash the process via a specially crafted NsPacked file.
			4) An incorrect regular expression in libclamav/phishcheck.c can be exploited to cause a DoS by consuming all available CPU resources via a specially crafted file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>213</id>
		<date>2007-07-01</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>gd</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.34-2terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.34-2terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2219</bts>
		<cve>No CVE for this issue, see: http://www.libgd.org/ReleaseNote020035</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in the GD Graphics Library, where some have unknown impact and others can potentially be exploited to cause a DoS.
			1) An integer overflow exists in the "gdImageCreateTrueColor()" function.
			2) An error in the "gdImageCreateXbm()" function can potentially be exploited to cause a crash.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>212</id>
		<date>2007-07-01</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>evolution-data-server</package>
		<vulnerable>1.10.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.10.0-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2207</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3257</cve>
		<desc>Philip Van Hoof has reported a vulnerability in Evolution, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the "imap_rescan()" function in camel/providers/imap/camel-imap-folder.c not properly sanitising the "SEQUENCE" value before being used to index arrays. This may be exploited to execute arbitrary code by e.g. tricking a user into using a malicious IMAP server.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>211</id>
		<date>2007-07-01</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libexif</package>
		<vulnerable>0.6.13-2terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.6.13-2terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2197</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4168</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in libexif, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow error within the "exif_data_load_data_entry()" function when handling EXIF component information and can be exploited to cause a heap based buffer overflow.
			Successful exploitation may allow an attacker to crash an application using the library or to execute arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>210</id>
		<date>2007-07-01</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>vlc</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.6-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.6-4terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2182</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3316</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in VLC Media Player, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to format string errors in the Ogg/Vorbis, Ogg/Theora, CDDA (CD Digital Audio), and SAP (Service Announce Protocol) plugins. These can be exploited to execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted .ogg or .ogm file (Vorbis/Theora), CDDB entry, or SAP/SDP message.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>209</id>
		<date>2007-06-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.20-5terminus5</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.20-5terminus6</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2160</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2453
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2875
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2876</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities and a weakness have been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose potentially sensitive information and malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) A NULL-pointer dereference exists within netfilter when handling new SCTP connections with unknown chunk types. This can be exploited to crash the kernel by sending malicious packets.
			2) An underflow error within the "cpuset_task_read()" function in /kernel/cpuset.c can be exploited to read kernel memory, which may contain potentially sensitive information. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has access to open the /dev/cpuset/tasks file (the cpuset file system needs to be mounted).
			3) The kernel does not handle seeds for the random number generator correctly. This may weaken the security of applications relying on the randomness of the kernel random number generator.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>208</id>
		<date>2007-06-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mutt-ng</package>
		<vulnerable>20070125-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>20070125-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2140</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2683</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in mutt, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges. Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code with another user's privileges, but requires that the malicious user has a specially crafted realname and exists in the target user's alias file.
			Also fixes http://dev.mutt.org/trac/ticket/2846</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>207</id>
		<date>2007-06-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>cacti</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.6j-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.6j-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2133</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3112
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3113</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in Cacti, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in graph_image.php, which can be exploited to use lots of system resources by passing malicious values to the "graph_start", "graph_end", "graph_width", and "graph_height" parameters.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>206</id>
		<date>2007-06-08</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mutt-devel</package>
		<vulnerable>1.5.14-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.5.14-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2139</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2683</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in mutt, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges. Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code with another user's privileges, but requires that the malicious user has a specially crafted realname and exists in the target user's alias file.
			Also fixes http://dev.mutt.org/trac/ticket/2846</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>205</id>
		<date>2007-06-08</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mplayer</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0rc1-4terminus2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0rc1-4terminus3</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2131</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2948</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered some vulnerabilities in MPlayer, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) A boundary error within the "cddb_query_parse()" function in stream/stream_cddb.c when parsing album titles can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow by tricking a user into parsing malicious CDDB entries via overly long album titles. Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.
			2) Boundary errors within the "cddb_parse_matches_list()" and "cddb_read_parse()" functions in stream/stream_cddb.c when parsing album and category titles can be exploited to cause stack-based buffer overflows by tricking a user into parsing malicious CDDB entries with overly long album or category titles. Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code, but may require that the user connects to a malicious server.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>204</id>
		<date>2007-06-08</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>findutils</package>
		<vulnerable>4.3.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.3.2-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2128</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2452</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in GNU findutils, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error when parsing "old" style formatted locate databases. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by e.g. tricking a user into running locate on a specially crafted "old" style database containing an overly long path (more than 1026 bytes).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>203</id>
		<date>2007-06-08</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>php</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2.2-1terminus2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2.3-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2127</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2872
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1900</cve>
		<desc>A weakness and a vulnerability have been reported in PHP 5, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) An integer overflow error in the "chunk_split()" function can be exploited to cause a heap based buffer overflow. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may allow execution of arbitrary code, which can lead to security restrictions, such as the "disable_functions" directive, being bypassed.
			2) An error in the "realpath()" function allows bypassing of the "open_basedir" restriction and identifying the existence of files.
			Stefan Esser has reported a vulnerability in PHP, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions. The vulnerability is caused due to the use of an incorrect regular expression within the "FILTER_VALIDATE_EMAIL" filter of the ext/filter extension. This can be exploited to inject newlines via specially crafted email addresses, which may allow mail header injection.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>202</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.20-5terminus4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.20-5terminus5</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2126</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2878</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service). The security issue is caused due to an error within the handling of certain VFAT IOCTLs on 64bit systems, which can be exploited to crash the kernel by calling certain IOCTLs with malicious parameters. Successful exploitation requires a 64bit-system and vfat and msdos file systems.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>201</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>thunderbird</package>
		<vulnerable>1.5.0.10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.5.0.12-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2124</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2867
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2868</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Mozilla Thunderbird, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system. Errors in the JavaScript engine can be exploited to cause memory corruption and potentially to execute arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>200</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mutt</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.2.2-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.2.2-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2120</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2683</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in mutt, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges. Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code with another user's privileges, but requires that the malicious user has a specially crafted realname and exists in the target user's alias file.
			Also fixes http://dev.mutt.org/trac/ticket/2846</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>199</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>gd</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.34-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.34-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2074</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2756</cve>
		<desc>Xavier Roche has reported a vulnerability in GD Graphics Library, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service). The vulnerability is caused due to the incorrect use of libpng within the function "gdPngReadData()" when processing truncated data. This can be exploited to cause an infinite loop by e.g. tricking an application using the library to process a specially crafted file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>198</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>seamonkey</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.2-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2123</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2867
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2868
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2870
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2871</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mozilla SeaMonkey, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct spoofing attacks, bypass certain security restrictions, and potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) Errors in the JavaScript engine can be exploited to cause memory corruption and potentially to execute arbitrary code.
			2) An error in the "addEventListener" method can be exploited to inject script into another site, circumventing the browser's same-origin policy. This could be used to access or modify sensitive information from the other site.
			3) An error in the handling of XUL popups can be exploited to spoof parts of the browser such as the location bar.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>197</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.3-1terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.4-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2125</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2867
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2868
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2870
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2871</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct spoofing attacks, bypass certain security restrictions, and potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) Errors in the JavaScript engine can be exploited to cause memory corruption and potentially to execute arbitrary code.
			2) An error in the "addEventListener" method can be exploited to inject script into another site, circumventing the browser's same-origin policy. This could be used to access or modify sensitive information from the other site.
			3) An error in the handling of XUL popups can be exploited to spoof parts of the browser such as the location bar.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>196</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>xfsprogs-xfsdump</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.38_1-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.2.45_1-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2122</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2654</cve>
		<desc>Paul Martin has reported a security issue in xfsdump, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose potentially sensitive information or manipulate data. The security issue is caused due to xfs_fsr creating a temporary directory with insecure permissions within the function "tmp_init()" in fsr/xfs_fsr.c. This can be exploited to read or overwrite files created in this directory or subdirectories, potentially allowing for the disclosure of sensitive information or data manipulation.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>195</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>tor</package>
		<vulnerable>0.1.1.26-3terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.1.2.14-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2121</bts>
		<cve>No CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>lodger has reported a weakness in Tor, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to expose sensitive information. When building a circuit, Tor checks if an entry guard is exactly the same as an exit guard, but fails to check if they are also part of the same family. This may weaken the Tor security concept and could make it easier to launch certain attacks.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>194</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>file</package>
		<vulnerable>4.20-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.21-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2119</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1536
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2799</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in file, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system. The vulnerability is caused due to an unspecified integer underflow within the "file_printf" function, which can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>193</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>tcl</package>
		<vulnerable>8.4.14-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>8.4.15-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2118</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2877</cve>
		<desc>Martin Lemburg has reported a security issue in Tcl, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges. The security issue is caused due to a boundary error within tcl/win/tclWinReg.c when processing overly long registry key names. This can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow by e.g. creating a malicious registry key and enticing another user to query it with an application using Tcl.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>192</id>
		<date>2007-06-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.20-5terminus3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.20-5terminus4</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2097</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2480
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2525</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in the Linux Kernel, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or disclose potentially sensitive information.
			1) A memory leak exists when releasing PPPoE sockets after they are connected, but before the "PPPIOCGCHAN" ioctl is called. This can be exploited to cause a DoS due to memory exhaustion.
			2) An error within the "_udp_lib_get_port()" function in net/ipv4/udp.c can be exploited to intercept traffic by binding to a port using a local address if a wildcard bind exists with a local address to that port.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>191</id>
		<date>2007-05-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>freetype2</package>
		<vulnerable>2.3.4-1terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.3.4-1terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2073</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2754</cve>
		<desc>Victor Stinner has reported a vulnerability in FreeType, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error when parsing malformed TTF fonts in src/truetype/ttgload.c and may be exploited when processing a specially crafted TTF font.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>190</id>
		<date>2007-05-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>zoo</package>
		<vulnerable>2.10-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.10-5terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2065</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1669</cve>
		<desc>It's possible to make the ZOO implementation to enter in an infinite loop condition.  The vulnerability lies in the algorithm used to locate the files inside the archive.  Each file in a ZOO archive is identified by a direntry structure.  Those structures are linked between themselves with a 'next' pointer.  This pointer is in fact an offset from the beginning of the file, representing the next direntry structure.  By specifying an already processed file, it's possible to process more than one time this same file.  The ZOO parser will then enter an infinite loop condition.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>189</id>
		<date>2007-05-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>vmware</package>
		<vulnerable>5.5.3_34685-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.5.4_44386-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2009</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1069
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1337
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1744
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1876
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1877</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in various VMware products, which can be exploited by malicious users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) An error exists within the ACPI implementation of the virtual machine process (VMX) when collecting information about running states of virtual machines, which can be exploited to cause the process to read from invalid memory locations.
			2) An error within the saving of configuration data in VMDB files can be exploited to store malformed configuration data and cause a DoS on guest operating systems.
			3) An error within the handling of general protection faults (GPFs) in Windows guest operating systems can be exploited to crash Windows virtual machines.
			4) Errors when debugging applications in a 64-bit Windows guest operating system on a 64-bit host system can be exploited to e.g. cause corrupted stack pointers or kernel bugchecks.
			5) A design error within the "Shared Folders" feature can be exploited in a guest system to read and write arbitrary files on a host system.
			Successful exploitation requires that at least one folder is shared. In order to write to host files, the "read only" option of the shared folder has to be disabled. ESX server is reportedly not affected as it does not use the "Shared Folders" feature.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>188</id>
		<date>2007-05-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>madwifi</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.3-1terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.3.1-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2078</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for these issues</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in MadWifi, which can be exploited by malicious, local users and malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) A division by zero error exists within the function "ath_beacon_config()". This can be exploited to cause a crash by sending a packet with a zero beacon interval to a vulnerable system.
			2) An input sanitation error exists within the IO control "ieee80211_ioctl_getwmmparams". This can be exploited to crash the kernel by calling the IO control with a negative index parameter. This may also allow certain parts of the memory to be disclosed.
			3) An input sanitation error exist within the packet parser when parsing nested 802.3 Ethernet frame lengths. This can be exploited to cause a NULL pointer dereference by sending a specially crafted fast frame packet to a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>187</id>
		<date>2007-05-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>php</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2.2-1terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2.2-1terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2075</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2756</cve>
		<desc>Xavier Roche has reported a vulnerability in PHP, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to the incorrect use of libpng within the function "gdPngReadData()" in ext/gd/libgd/gd_png.c of the GD extension when processing truncated data. This can be exploited to cause an infinite loop by e.g. tricking an application to process a specially crafted file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>186</id>
		<date>2007-05-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>jasper</package>
		<vulnerable>1.900.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.900.1-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2066</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2721</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in JasPer, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the "jpc_qcx_getcompparms" function when processing JP2 files and can be exploited to crash an application using the library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>185</id>
		<date>2007-05-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>samba samba-client</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.24-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.24-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2050</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2444
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2446
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2447</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Samba, which can be exploited by malicious users to perform certain actions with escalated privileges and to compromise a vulnerable system, and by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) An error in smbd when translating SIDs to and from names can be exploited to issue SMB/CIFS protocol operations as the root user. Successful exploitation requires a valid user session.
			2) An input validation error when updating a user's password can be exploited to inject and execute arbitrary shell commands via a specially crafted MS-RPC call.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires that the "username map script" option is set in smb.conf, which is not the default setting. In addition, to successfully exploit this vulnerability via remote printer and file share management, an attacker requires a valid user session.
			3) Input validation errors exist in the parsing of RPC requests to the LSA RPC interface. This can be exploited to cause heap based buffer overflows via specially crafted requests to "LsarAddPrivilegesToAccount", "LsarLookupSids", or "LsarLookupSids2".
			4) An input validation error exists in the parsing of RPC requests to the DFS RPC interface. This can be exploited to cause a heap based buffer overflow via a specially crafted request to "DFSEnum".
			5) An input validation error exists in the parsing of RPC requests to the SPOOLSS RPC interface. This can be exploited to cause a heap based buffer overflow via a specially crafted request to "RFNPCNEX".
			6) An input validation error exists in the parsing of RPC requests to the SRVSVC RPC interface. This can be exploited to cause a heap based buffer overflow via a specially crafted request to "NetSetFileSecurity".
			Successful exploitation of vulnerabilities #3 through #6 allows execution of arbitrary code, but requires a valid user session.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>184</id>
		<date>2007-05-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libpng</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.16-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.16-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2051</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2445</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in libpng, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the "png_handle_tRNS" function in pngrutil.c. This can be exploited by tricking an application using the library to process a specially crafted PNG file containing a malformed tRNS chunk.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>183</id>
		<date>2007-05-13</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>asterisk</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.2-2terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.2-2terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1985
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2030</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2293
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2294
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2297
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2488</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Asterisk, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) Two boundary errors exist in the T.38 SDP parser of the SIP channel when processing the "T38FaxRateManagement" or "T38FaxUdpEC" SDP parameters within the "process_sdp()" function in chan_sip.c. This can be exploited to cause stack-based buffer overflows by sending a specially crafted SIP packet with overly long SDP parameters. Successful exploitation requires that the "t38_udptl" configuration option is set to "yes".
			2) A NULL pointer dereference error exists within the authentication mechanism of the Asterisk Remote Management Interface, which can be exploited to crash the service. Successful exploitation requires that the Management Interface is enabled and a user without a password is configured in the manager.conf file.
			A vulnerability has been reported in Asterisk, which can be exploited by malicious users to disclose potential sensitive information.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the IAX2 channel driver (chan_iax2) in the processing of text frames. This can be exploited to disclose potentially sensitive heap memory by sending a text frame with content that is not NULL terminated.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>182</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mysql</package>
		<vulnerable>5.0.37-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.0.37-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2037</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2583</cve>
		<desc>Neil Kettle has reported a vulnerability in MySQL, which can be exploited by malicious users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error when handling specially crafted IF queries, which can be exploited to crash the server.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>181</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>php</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2.1-3terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2.2-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2014</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1864
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2509
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2510
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2511</cve>
		<desc>Several vulnerabilities and weaknesses have been reported in PHP, where some have unknown impacts and others can be exploited by malicious users to manipulate certain data, disclose potentially sensitive information, bypass certain security restrictions, or to cause a DoS (Denial of Service), and potentially by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) An input validation error in the "ftp_putcmd()" function can be exploited to inject newline characters.
			2) An unspecified error in the "import_request_variables()" can be exploited to overwrite global variables.
			3) An unspecified error can remotely be exploited to cause a buffer overflow within in the "make_http_soap_request()" function (PHP 5).
			4) An unspecified error can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow within the "user_filter_factory_create()" function (PHP 5).
			5) An unspecified error in the bundled libxmlrpc library can remotely be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow and may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			6) An input validation error in the "mail()" function allows injection of headers via the "To" and "Subject" parameters.
			7) An error in the "mail()" function allows to truncate messages via ASCIIZ bytes.
			8) The "safe_mode" and "open_basedir" protection mechanisms can be bypassed via the "zip://" and "bzip://" wrappers.
			9) An integer overflow exists in "substr_compare()", which can be exploited to read memory from memory behind PHP variables. The "substr_count" function is reportedly also affected.
			10) An error in the "mb_parse_str()" can be exploited to activate "register_globals".
			11) An error in the Zend engine related to nested array variables that can be exploited to crash a PHP application.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>180</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>xscreensaver</package>
		<vulnerable>5.01-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.01-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2013</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1859</cve>
		<desc>Alex Yamauchi has reported a weakness in XScreenSaver, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The weakness is caused due to an error within the parsing of results of a call to "getpwuid()" in drivers/lock.c when using directory servers during a network outage. This can be exploited to e.g. crash XScreenSaver and thus gain access to a locked system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>179</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>xmms</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.10-11</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.10-12terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1854</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0653
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0654</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered two vulnerabilities in XMMS, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) An integer underflow error exists in the processing of skin bitmap images. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow via specially crafted skin images containing manipulated header information.	Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.
			2) An integer overflow error exists in the processing of skin bitmap images. This can be exploited to cause memory corruption via specially crafted skin images containing manipulated header information. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>178</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libexif</package>
		<vulnerable>0.6.13-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.6.13-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2043</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>Victor Stinner has reported a vulnerability in libexif, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS and potentially compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the handling of malformed EXIF information. This can be exploited to crash an application using the library and may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>177</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>gimp</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.13-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.2.13-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2007</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2356</cve>
		<desc>Marsu has discovered a vulnerability in Gimp, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the "set_color_table()" function in plug-ins/common/sunras.c. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted .RAS file.
			Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>176</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>squirrelmail</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.9-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.10-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2034</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1262</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in SquirrelMail, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting and cross-site request forgery attacks.
			1) SquirrelMail does not sanitise charsets in HTML or JavaScript data before sending it to browsers. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site by sending malicious HTML emails. Reportedly, this affects Internet Explorer only.
			2) The script compose.php allows users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing validity checks to verify the request. This can be exploited to e.g. send emails from another user's account by including malicious links to images in an email.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>175</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>python</package>
		<vulnerable>2.5-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.5-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2033</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2052</cve>
		<desc>Piotr Engelking has reported a security issue in Python, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose potentially sensitive information.
			The security issue is caused due to an off-by-one error within the "PyLocale_strxfrm()" function in Modules/_localemodule.c, which can be exploited to disclose certain parts of the memory.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>174</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>vim</package>
		<vulnerable>7.0-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>7.0-4terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2010</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2438</cve>
		<desc>Tomas Golembiovsky has discovered a vulnerability in Vim, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the application allowing e.g. the "feedkeys()" function to be called in the sandbox. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary commands with privileges of the Vim user.
			Successful exploitation requires that the "modelines" option is enabled and the user is tricked into opening a malicious file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>173</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>bind</package>
		<vulnerable>9.4.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.4.1-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2008</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2241</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in BIND, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error when invoking the "query_addsoa()" function. This can be exploited to cause the nameserver to exit by sending a specially crafted sequence of queries.
			Successful exploitation requires that "recursion" is enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>172</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>elinks</package>
		<vulnerable>0.11.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.11.2-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2031</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2027</cve>
		<desc>Arnaud Giersch has reported a weakness in ELinks, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			The weakness is caused due to the "add_filename_to_string()" function in src/intl/gettext/loadmsgcat.c reading gettext catalogs from potentially untrusted paths. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary code with escalated privileges by enticing another user to run ELinks in a specially prepared directory environment.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>171</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>unzip</package>
		<vulnerable>5.52-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.52-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2026</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2005-2475
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2005-4667</cve>
		<desc>Race condition in Unzip 5.52 allows local users to modify permissions of arbitrary files via a hard link attack on a file while it is being decompressed, whose permissions are changed by Unzip after the decompression is complete.
			Buffer overflow in UnZip allows user-assisted attackers to execute arbitrary code via a long filename command line argument. NOTE: since the overflow occurs in a non-setuid program, there are not many scenarios under which it poses a vulnerability, unless unzip is passed long arguments when it is invoked from other programs.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>170</id>
		<date>2007-05-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.20-5terminus2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.20-5terminus3</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2006</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2172
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2242
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1861</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities and a security issue have been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) An error exists within the processing of packets with IPv6 type 0 route headers. This can be exploited to cause a DoS due to high network traffic by sending specially crafted IPv6 packets to vulnerable systems.
			2) A boundary error due to the use of RTA_MAX instead of RTN_MAX in dn_fib_props[] within dn_fib.c and in fib_props[] within fib_semantics.c can potentially be exploited to cause a DoS.
			3) The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the handling of NETLINK_FIB_LOOKUP reply messages. This can be exploited to cause an infinite recursion, which could result in a stack overflow.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>169</id>
		<date>2007-05-10</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>truecrypt</package>
		<vulnerable>4.3-1terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.3-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2024</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue</cve>
		<desc>When running without administrator privileges, TrueCrypt automatically attempts to elevate its access rights (if necessary) using the sudo command. The Linux version of TrueCrypt no longer supports the set-euid root mode of execution. These changes also prevent all discovered and undiscovered (if any) security issues related to the set-euid root mode of execution, including an issue affecting all previous Linux versions of TrueCrypt where a local non-administrator user could cause a denial of service or gain administrator privileges.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>168</id>
		<date>2007-05-10</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>postgresql</package>
		<vulnerable>8.2.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>8.2.4-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1983</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2138</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in PostgreSQL, which potentially can be exploited by malicious users to gain escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused due to an error in SECURITY DEFINER functions and can be exploited to gain escalated privileges by modifying the search_path and using temporary objects.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>167</id>
		<date>2007-05-10</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>proftpd</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.0-6</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.0-7terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1981</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2165</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in ProFTPD, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The security issue is caused due to an error within ProFTPD's Auth API. If multiple authentication modules are used, it is possible that one module provides data, which is then authenticated against another module. This can e.g. be exploited to bypass certain security restrictions if authentication modules are configured with different policies.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>166</id>
		<date>2007-05-10</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>php</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2.1-2terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2.1-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1962
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1841
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2014</bts>
		<cve>http://www.cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1001
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1521
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1484
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1649
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1900</cve>
		<desc>Ivan Fratric has reported a vulnerability in PHP, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service). The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow within the "readwbmp()" function in ext/gd/libgd/wbmp.c. This can be exploited to e.g. cause a DoS by tricking a PHP script into loading a specially crafted wbmp image.
			Stefan Esser has reported some vulnerabilities in PHP, which can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) A double free error within the "session_regenerate_id()" function can be exploited to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the PHP interpreter.
			2) An error in the "array_user_key_compare()" function where key references are incorrectly destroyed can be exploited to cause memory corruption.
			3) An error exists within the "unserialize()" function when unserialising specially escaped S: data types. This can be exploited to e.g. disclose certain parts of the heap memory.
			A vulnerability is caused due to the use of an incorrect regular expression within the "FILTER_VALIDATE_EMAIL" filter of the ext/filter extension. This can be exploited to inject newlines via specially crafted email addresses, which may allow mail header injection.
			Also fixes the following MOPB vulnerabilities:
			http://www.php-security.org/MOPB/MOPB-10-2007.html
			http://www.php-security.org/MOPB/MOPB-14-2007.html
			http://www.php-security.org/MOPB/MOPB-26-2007.html
			http://www.php-security.org/MOPB/MOPB-34-2007.html
			http://www.php-security.org/MOPB/MOPB-41-2007.html</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>165</id>
		<date>2007-05-09</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>smb4k</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.3-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1935</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue, see https://developer.berlios.de/project/shownotes.php?release_id=12615</cve>
		<desc>Ben Hutchings discovered the following security weaknesses in the utility programs:
			Due to insufficient sanitation, smb4k_mount allowed an user to mount any (local) device if the program was used in combination with sudo or super.
			The function findprog(), which was in present smb4k_mount, smb4k_umount, and smb4k_kill, returned a pointer to memory that was freed when the function exited.
			The function replace_special_characters(), that was present in smb4k_mount and smb4k_umount, returned a pointer to memory that was freed after the function exited. Additionally, it didn't replace the hyphen.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>164</id>
		<date>2007-05-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>ktorrent</package>
		<vulnerable>2.1.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.1.4-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2012</bts>
		<cve>http://www.cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1384
			http://www.cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1385
			http://www.cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1799</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in KTorrent, which can be exploited by malicious people to overwrite arbitrary files on a user's system or to potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) An input validation error when processing paths of filenames within torrents can be exploited to e.g. overwrite arbitrary files with the privileges of the user running the application via directory traversal attacks.
			2) An error in the processing of messages with invalid chunk indexes can be exploited to corrupt memory and may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>163</id>
		<date>2007-05-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>lesstif</package>
		<vulnerable>0.95.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.95.0-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1967</bts>
		<cve>http://www.cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2005-0605</cve>
		<desc>The XPM library's scan.c file may allow attackers to execute arbitrary code by crafting a malicious XPM image file containing a negative bitmap_unit value that provokes a buffer overflow.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>162</id>
		<date>2007-05-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.10.0.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.10.1-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1984</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2245</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Input passed to the "fieldkey" parameter in browse_foreigners.php and input passed to the "PMA_sanitize()" function is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>161</id>
		<date>2007-04-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>imagemagick</package>
		<vulnerable>6.3.2_8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.3.2_8-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1913</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1797</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in ImageMagick, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) A integer overflow error within the "ReadDCMImage()" function can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow when processing specially crafted DCM images.
			2) Two integer overflows within the "ReadXWDImage()" function when calculating the amount of memory to be allocated for the 'colors' or 'comment' fields can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows when processing specially crafted XWD images.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>160</id>
		<date>2007-04-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.20-5terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.20-5terminus2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1934</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1357</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the "atalk_sum_skb()" function when creating the checksum of an AppleTalk frame that is shorter than specified in the header. This can be exploited to trigger a "BUG_ON" condition by sending a specially crafted AppleTalk frame to a vulnerable system.
			Successful exploitation requires that the AppleTalk kernel module is loaded.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>159</id>
		<date>2007-04-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>firefox-firebug</package>
		<vulnerable>1.01-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.05-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1917</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1878
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1947</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in the Firebug extension for Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) Input passed to the "console.log()" function is not properly sanitised and can be exploited to e.g. execute arbitrary script code within the "chrome:" context by tricking a user into visiting a malicious website.
			2) Results of the "toString" method when processing function objects are not properly sanitised before being used. This can be exploited to e.g. execute arbitrary script code within the "chrome:" context by overriding the "toString" method with a specially crafted function.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>158</id>
		<date>2007-04-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>opera</package>
		<vulnerable>9.10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.20-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1757</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0995
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1115
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2022</cve>
		<desc>Stefan Esser has discovered a vulnerability in Opera, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			The vulnerability exist because pages that do not specify a charset inherit the charset of the parent page. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of certain sites that are included e.g. via iframes in a malicious page that uses UTF-7 as charset.
			Successful exploitation requires that the user is tricked into visiting a malicious web site.
			A vulnerability with an unknown impact has been reported in Opera. The vulnerability is caused due to an unspecified error when using the Adobe Flash Player plug-in.
			The vulnerability is reported in Opera versions prior to 9.20 running on Linux, Solaris, or FreeBSD and using the Adobe Flash Player version 7 or 9.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>157</id>
		<date>2007-04-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>2.1.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.1.3-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1837</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1894
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1622
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1893
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1897</cve>
		<desc>g30rg3_x has discovered a vulnerability in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks. Input passed to the "year" parameter when used in wp_title() is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			A vulnerability has been discovered in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks. Input passed to the "PHP_SELF" variable is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			Sumit Siddharth has discovered two vulnerabilities in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct SQL injection attacks or to bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) Input passed to the "mt.setPostCategories" method in xmlrpc.php is not properly sanitised before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code. Successful exploitation allows e.g. retrieving usernames and password hashes, but requires valid user credentials.
			2) A vulnerability is caused due to improper authentication verification in xmlrpc.php. A user with contributor permissions can exploit this issue to publish posts. Successful exploitation requires valid user credentials.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>156</id>
		<date>2007-04-17</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>aircrack-ng</package>
		<vulnerable>0.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.7-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1947</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue, see: http://secunia.com/advisories/24880</cve>
		<desc>Jonathan So has reported a vulnerability in Aircrack-ng, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system. The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the airodump-ng module when processing 802.11 authentication packets. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted 802.11 packet. Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code and requires that the application is logging packets with the -w or --write option.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>155</id>
		<date>2007-04-17</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>clamav</package>
		<vulnerable>0.90.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.90.2-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1946</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1745
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1997</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in Clam AntiVirus. One has an unknown impact, while the other can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) An unspecified file descriptor leak error exists within libclamav/chmunpack.c.
			2) A signedness error exists within the "cab_unstore()" function in libclamav/cab.c. This can be exploited to cause a stack based buffer overflow via a specially crafted ".cab" file, and may allow execution of arbitrary code or crashing of the clamd process.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>154</id>
		<date>2007-04-16</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>lighttpd</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.13-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.13-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1951</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1869
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1870</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in lighttpd, which can be exploited by malicious users and malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) An error exists during the parsing of the "\r\n\r\n" sequence. This can be exploited to cause an infinite loop by aborting the connection while the server parses the sequence, which e.g. results in a high CPU load and exhaustion of system resources .
			2) An NULL pointer dereference exists within the mtime handling of files. This can be exploited to cause a crash by requesting a file with mtime 0. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker can request or upload files with mtime 0, or can otherwise modify the mtime of files.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>153</id>
		<date>2007-04-11</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>qt4</package>
		<vulnerable>4.2.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.2.3-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1909</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0242</cve>
		<desc>Andreas Nolden has reported a vulnerability in Qt, which potentially can be exploited to conduct cross-site scripting attacks in applications using the Qt libraries. The vulnerability is caused due to Qt not properly rejecting overly long UTF-8 character sequences. This can be exploited to bypass certain character sanitation mechanisms and allow e.g. the execution of HTML and script code in applications depending on the correct behavior.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>152</id>
		<date>2007-04-11</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>madwifi</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.2.1-9terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.3-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1914</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-7178
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-7179
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-7180</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in MadWifi, which can be exploited by malicious people to gain knowledge of potentially sensitive information or cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) An error within the "ieee80211_input()" function when handling AUTH frames from IBSS nodes can be exploited to cause a kernel crash by sending specially crafted AUTH frames. Successful exploitation may require that the "Ad-Hoc" mode is used.
			2) MadWifi does not correctly handle Channel Switch Announcements. This can be exploited to force a channel switch thus interrupting the communication by injecting a Channel Switch Announcement with "CS Count" set to 1 or less.
			3) An error within ieee80211_output.c may cause unencrypted packets to be sent before the WPA authentication is completed. This can be exploited to gain knowledge of certain sensitive information, which may be leveraged for further attacks.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>151</id>
		<date>2007-04-11</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mod_perl</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.3-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1894</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1349</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in mod_perl, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).	The vulnerability is caused due to a regular expression in "RegistryCooker.pm" (mod_perl 2.x) or "PerlRun.pm" (mod_perl 1.x) that uses the "path_info" variable without properly escaping it. This can be exploited to cause a DoS by sending requests with specially crafted URLs to a vulnerable server.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>150</id>
		<date>2007-04-11</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>asterisk</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.2-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1853</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1561
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1594
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1595</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Asterisk, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service). The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the handling of certain SIP INVITE messages. This can be exploited to crash the server by sending a SIP INVITE message with 2 SDP headers, where the second header contains an invalid IP address. Successful exploitation requires that the callee is an invalid dailplan or user.
			qwerty1979 has reported a vulnerability in Asterisk, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service). The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the processing of SIP replies from a remote system and can be exploited to crash the service via the remote system sending a SIP reply containing SIP Response code 0.
			A security issue has been reported in Asterisk, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions. The security issue is caused due to a problem within the AEL (Asterisk Extension Language) when generating switch extensions. Depending on the extension, an attacker may be able to guess and dial a special number, which could allow him to e.g. listen to the voicemails of other users.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>149</id>
		<date>2007-04-07</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>freetype2</package>
		<vulnerable>2.3.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.3.3-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1916</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1351</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in FreeType, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow when parsing BDF fonts. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted BDF font.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>148</id>
		<date>2007-04-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>xorg-server</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.0-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1910</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1003
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1351
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1667</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in X.Org X11, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose sensitive information, cause a DoS (Denial of Service), and gain escalated privileges.
			1) An integer overflow exists within the parsing of BDF fonts. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted BDF font. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges.
			2) An integer overflow exists within the parsing of the "fonts.dir" fonts information file. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted fonts information file that specifies an element count of more than 1,073,741,824 in the first line. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges.
			3) An input validation error exists within the "ProcXCMiscGetXIDList()" function of the XC-MISC extension. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based (if the "alloca()" function is available) or heap-based memory corruption by passing specially crafted parameters to the function. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges.
			4) An integer overflow exists within the "XGetPixel()" function in ImUtil.c. This can be exploited to cause a crash or disclose potentially sensitive information by passing specially crafted parameters to the function.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>147</id>
		<date>2007-04-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libxfont</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.7-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1912</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1003
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1351
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1667</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in X.Org X11, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose sensitive information, cause a DoS (Denial of Service), and gain escalated privileges.
			1) An integer overflow exists within the parsing of BDF fonts. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted BDF font. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges.
			2) An integer overflow exists within the parsing of the "fonts.dir" fonts information file. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted fonts information file that specifies an element count of more than 1,073,741,824 in the first line. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges.
			3) An input validation error exists within the "ProcXCMiscGetXIDList()" function of the XC-MISC extension. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based (if the "alloca()" function is available) or heap-based memory corruption by passing specially crafted parameters to the function. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges.
			4) An integer overflow exists within the "XGetPixel()" function in ImUtil.c. This can be exploited to cause a crash or disclose potentially sensitive information by passing specially crafted parameters to the function.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>146</id>
		<date>2007-04-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libx11</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.1-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1911</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1003
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1351
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1667</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in X.Org X11, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose sensitive information, cause a DoS (Denial of Service), and gain escalated privileges.
			1) An integer overflow exists within the parsing of BDF fonts. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted BDF font. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges.
			2) An integer overflow exists within the parsing of the "fonts.dir" fonts information file. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted fonts information file that specifies an element count of more than 1,073,741,824 in the first line. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges.
			3) An input validation error exists within the "ProcXCMiscGetXIDList()" function of the XC-MISC extension. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based (if the "alloca()" function is available) or heap-based memory corruption by passing specially crafted parameters to the function. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code with escalated privileges.
			4) An integer overflow exists within the "XGetPixel()" function in ImUtil.c. This can be exploited to cause a crash or disclose potentially sensitive information by passing specially crafted parameters to the function.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>145</id>
		<date>2007-04-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>truecrypt</package>
		<vulnerable>4.2a-7terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.3-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1879</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1589
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1738</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in TrueCrypt, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service). The problem is that users are able to dismount volumes mounted by other users when the set-euid mode in Linux is used.
			Tim Rees has discovered a security issue in TrueCrypt, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or gain escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused if the "truecrypt" binary is installed setuid root. This can be exploited to cause a DoS or gain escalated privileges by e.g. mounting a malicious TrueCrypt disk into /usr/bin or another user's home directory. Successful exploitation requires that TrueCrypt is installed setuid root (not default setting).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>144</id>
		<date>2007-04-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>xine-lib</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.4-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.4-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1839</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1246
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1387</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in xine-lib, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to boundary errors in the "DMO_VideoDecoder_Open()" function in src/libw32dll/dmo/DMO_VideoDecoder.c and in the "DS_VideoDecoder_Open()" function in src/libw32dll/DirectShow/DS_VideoDecoder.c. These can be exploited to cause heap based buffer overflows and may allow execution of arbitrary code via a specially crafted media file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>143</id>
		<date>2007-04-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>evolution</package>
		<vulnerable>2.10.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.10.0-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1852</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1002</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered a vulnerability in Evolution, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			A format string error in the "write_html()" function in calendar/gui/e-cal-component-memo-preview.c when displaying a memo's categories can potentially be exploited to execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted shared memo containing format specifiers.
			Successful exploitation requires that the user opens a shared memo in their mailbox, clicks on "Accept", and views the memo under the "Memo" tab.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>142</id>
		<date>2007-04-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openoffice.org</package>
		<vulnerable>2.1.0-5</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.1.0-6terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1856</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0002
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0238
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0239</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in OpenOffice.org, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) Several vulnerabilities within the libwpd library used by OpenOffice.org can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows and may allow the execution of arbitrary code by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted WordPerfect document.
			2) A boundary error within the StarCalc parser can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow and may allow execution of arbitrary code by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted document.
			3) Shell meta characters are not correctly escaped, which can be exploited to inject and execute arbitrary shell commands by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted document and clicking a malicious link.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>141</id>
		<date>2007-03-28</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>nas</package>
		<vulnerable>1.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.8-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1843</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1543
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1544
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1545
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1546
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1547</cve>
		<desc>Luigi Auriemma has reported some vulnerabilities in Network Audio System, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges or by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) A boundary error within "accept_att_local()" in server/os/connection.c can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow via an overly long (greater than 64 bytes) slave name in a USL connection. Successful exploitation may allow malicious, local users to gain root privileges.
			2) An input validation error within "AddResource()" in server/dia/resource.c can be exploited to cause the service to crash via a specially crafted packet with an invalid client ID.
			3) An integer-overflow error within "ProcAuWriteElement()" in server/dia/audispatch.c can be exploited to cause the service to crash via a specially crafted packet with an overly large max_samples value.
			4) A boundary error within "ProcAuSetElements()" in server/dia/audispatch.c can be exploited to cause the service to crash via a specially crafted packet with an overly large num_actions or numElements value.
			5) An input validation error within "compileInputs()" in server/dia/auutil.c can be exploited to cause the service to crash via a specially crafted packet with an invalid element number.
			6) A NULL-pointer dereference error when processing simultaneous connections can be exploited to cause the service to crash.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>140</id>
		<date>2007-03-28</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>inkscape</package>
		<vulnerable>0.45-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.45.1-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1857</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1463
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1464</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Inkscape, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) A format string error exists in certain dialogs. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary code by tricking the user into opening a specially crafted URI containing format string specifiers.
			2) A format string error exists in the Whiteboard Jabber client, which potentially can be exploited to execute arbitrary code. Successful exploitation requires that the user is logged in to a Jabber server.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>139</id>
		<date>2007-03-28</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.20-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.20-5terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1858</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1592</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) Listening IPv6 TCP sockets are incorrectly sharing the "ipv6_fl_socklist" IPv6 flowlist with child sockets. This can be exploited to e.g. cause a kernel crash by performing certain actions on IPv6 TCP sockets.
			2) The "hrtimer_forward()" does not correctly check for "timer->expires" overflows on 64bit machines. This can be exploited to cause a DoS by using very large timer values. Successful exploitation may require a 64bit machine and that high resolution timers are enabled.
			3) A NULL pointer dereference within the "do_ipv6_setsockopt()" function in net/ipv6/ipv6_sockglue.c can be exploited to cause a kernel crash by calling "setsockopt()" with malicious parameters.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>138</id>
		<date>2007-03-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>squid</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.STABLE10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.STABLE12-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1855</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1560</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Squid, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the processing of TRACE requests in squid/src/client_side.c. This can be exploited to crash the service via a specially crafted TRACE request.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>137</id>
		<date>2007-03-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.3-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1850</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue, see: http://www.mozilla.org/security/announce/2007/mfsa2007-11.html</cve>
		<desc>The FTP protocol includes the PASV (passive) command which is used by Firefox to request an alternate data port. The specification of the FTP protocol allows the server response to include an alternate server address as well, although this is rarely used in practice.
			mark@bindshell.net reported that a malicious web page hosted on a specially-coded FTP server could use this feature to perform a rudimentary port-scan of machines inside the firewall of the victim. By itself this causes no harm, but information about an internal network may be useful to an attacker should there be other vulnerabilities present on the network.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>136</id>
		<date>2007-03-24</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libwpd</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.9-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1842</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0002
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1466</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in libwpd, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to compromise an application using the library.
			1) An integer overflow within the "WP6GeneralTextPacket::_readContents" function can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted WordPerfect document in an application using the library.
			2) Boundary errors within the "WP3TablesGroup::_readContents()" and "WP5DefinitionGroup_DefineTablesSubGroup::WP5DefinitionGroup_DefineTablesSubGroup()" functions can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted WordPerfect document in an application using the library.
			Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>135</id>
		<date>2007-03-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mplayer</package>
		<vulnerable>mplayer-1.0rc1-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>mplayer-1.0rc1-4terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1838</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1246
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1387</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in MPlayer, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to boundary errors in the "DMO_VideoDecoder_Open()" function in loader/dmo/DMO_VideoDecoder.c and in the "DS_VideoDecoder_Open()" function in loader/dshow/DS_VideoDecoder.c. These can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows and may allow execution of arbitrary code via a specially crafted media file.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
