<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author?, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- If you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - read /hooks/README! -->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>726</id>
		<date>2011-06-24</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>libreoffice</package>
		<vulnerable>3.3.0.4-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.3.3.1-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4518</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see
			http://www.kb.cert.org/vuls/id/953183</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in LibreOffice, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to errors in the import filter when processing Lotus Word Pro (LWP) files and can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted file.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code, but requires tricking a user into opening a malicious LWP file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>725</id>
		<date>2011-06-07</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.6-1nexon1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.7-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4510</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1956
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1957
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1958
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1959
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2174
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2175</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) An error in the DICOM dissector can be exploited to cause an infinite loop when processing certain malformed packets.
			2) An error when processing a Diameter dictionary file can be exploited to cause the process to crash.
			3) An error when processing a snoop file can be exploited to cause the process to crash.
			4) An error when processing compressed capture data can be exploited to cause the process to crash.
			5) An error when processing a Visual Networks file can be exploited to cause the process to crash.
			6) An error in the "desegment_tcp()" function (epan/dissectors/packet-tcp.c) when handling certain TCP segments can be exploited to dereference a NULL pointer and crash the process.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>724</id>
		<date>2011-05-31</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>freetype2</package>
		<vulnerable>2.4.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.4.2-2nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4433</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3814
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3855</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in FreeType, which can be exploited to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise an application using the library.
			1) An error exists in the "ft_var_readpackedpoints()" function in src/truetype/ttgxvar.c when processing TrueType GX fonts and can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted font.
			2) An error within the "Ins_SHZ()" function in src/truetype/ttinterp.c when handling the "SHZ" bytecode instruction can be exploited to cause a crash and potentially execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted font.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>723</id>
		<date>2011-05-28</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-webform</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_3.6-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_3.11-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4499</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/1161954.</cve>
		<desc>Justin Klein Keane has discovered multiple vulnerabilities in the Webform module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users and malicious people to conduct script insertion attacks.
			1) Input passed via the "name" parameter when submitting a new webform field is not properly sanitised in sites/all/modules/webform/includes/webform.report.inc before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires the "create webform content" or "administer nodes" permission.
			2) Input passed via the filename when uploading a file through a webform is not properly sanitised in sites/all/modules/webform/components/file.inc before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>722</id>
		<date>2011-05-28</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal7</package>
		<vulnerable>7.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>7.2-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4498</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/1168756</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability and a security issue have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks and by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) An error in the Color module can be exploited to conduct script insertion attacks.
			For more information see vulnerability #2 in: FSA721.
			2) A security issue in the File module (modules/file/file.module) in combination with restrictions via a node access module can be exploited to disclose private files.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>721</id>
		<date>2011-05-28</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6</package>
		<vulnerable>6.20-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.22-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4497</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/1168756</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks and by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) Certain input passed via the URL is not properly sanitised in the Drupal error handler before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires that on-screen error display is enabled in admin/settings/error-reporting.
			2) Input passed via the color scheme values (e.g. "palette[bg]", "palette[text]", "palette[sideborders]", "palette[footer]", and "palette[titleslogan]") to index.php (when "q" is set to "admin/appearance/settings/bartik") when changing the color scheme is not properly sanitised before being used in a style sheet. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary CSS and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires the "Administer themes" privileges and the victim user is running a browser which executes certain JavaScript statements from CSS files (e.g. Internet Explorer 6).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>720</id>
		<date>2011-05-28</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>3.1.2-1nexon1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.1.3-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4496</bts>
		<cve>No CVE yet, see http://wordpress.org/news/2011/05/wordpress-3-1-3/</cve>
		<desc>neworder has discovered a vulnerability in the is_human() plugin for WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			Input passed to the "type" parameter in engine.php (when e.g. "action" is set to "log-reset") is not properly verified before being used in an "eval()" function and can be exploited to inject and execute arbitrary PHP code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>719</id>
		<date>2011-05-16</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.37-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.37-3nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4489</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0726
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1013
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1019
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1076</cve>
		<desc>Secutity issues have been reported in the Linux kernel:
		1) The start_code and end_code values in "/proc/[pid]/stat" were not protected. In certain scenarios, this flaw could be used to defeat Address Space Layout Randomization (ASLR).
		2) An integer signedness flaw in drm_modeset_ctl() could allow a local, unprivileged user to cause a denial of service or escalate their privileges.
		3) A flaw in dev_load() could allow a local user who has the CAP_NET_ADMIN capability to load arbitrary modules from "/lib/modules/", instead of only netdev modules.
		4) When a DNS resolver key is instantiated with an error indication, attempts to read that key resulted in an oops because user_read() expected there to be a payload - and there wasn't one.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>718</id>
		<date>2011-04-29</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>3.1.1-1nexon1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.1.2-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4478</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://codex.wordpress.org/Version_3.1.2</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The security issue is caused due to wp-admin/press-this.php script not properly checking a user's permissions before publishing posts and can be exploited by users without the "publish_posts" permission.
			Successful exploitation requires "Contributor-level" privileges.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>717</id>
		<date>2011-04-20</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.4-1nexon1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.6-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4472</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1590
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1591</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
1) A use-after-free error within the X.509if dissector can be exploited to cause a crash via specially crafted packets.
2) An error in the DECT dissector can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow via specially crafted packets.
Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>716</id>
		<date>2011-04-10</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.5-1nexon1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.1.1-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4464</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://wordpress.org/news/2011/04/wordpress-3-1-1/</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
1) Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
2) The "make_clickable()" function in wp-includes/formatting.php does not properly check the URL length in comments before passing it to the PCRE library, which can be exploited to cause a crash.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>715</id>
		<date>2011-04-10</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.4-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4443</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0538
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0713
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1138
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1139
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1140
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1141
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1142
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-1143</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
1) An error when processing certain pcap-ng files can be exploited to free an uninitialised pointer.
2) An error when handling certain packet lengths can be exploited to cause a crash via a specially crafted pcap-ng file.
3) An error when processing Nokia DCT3 trace files can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow via a specially crafted file.
Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may allow execution of arbitrary code.
4) An error in the "dissect_ms_compressed_string()" (SMB dissector) and "dissect_mscldap_string()" (LDAP dissector) functions can be exploited to cause a crash due to an infinite recursive function call.
5) An error when processing LDAP Filter strings can be exploited to cause a crash by consuming memory resources via large filter strings.
6) A validation error in the "dissect_6lowpan_iphc()" function (epan/dissectors/packet-6lowpan.c) in the 6LoWPAN dissector when processing certain lengths can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow of a single byte resulting in a crash.
7) A NULL pointer dereference error within the "dissect_ntlmssp_string()" function in epan/dissectors/packet-ntlmssp.c when parsing a pcap file can be exploited to cause a crash.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>714</id>
		<date>2011-04-10</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.5-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4427</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0700
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0701</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks and disclose potentially sensitive information and by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
1) Input passed via the post title when performing a "Quick Edit" or "Bulk Edit" action and via the "post_status", "comment_status", and "ping_status" parameters is not properly sanitised before being used. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
2) Certain input passed via tags in the tags meta-box is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities requires the "Author" or "Contributor" role.
3) The application incorrectly enforces user access restrictions when accessing posts via the media uploader and can be exploited to disclose the contents of e.g. private or draft posts.
Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires the "Author" role.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>713</id>
		<date>2011-04-10</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>3.3.9-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.3.9.2-1nexon1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4424</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0987</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions.
The security issue is caused due to an error within the handling of bookmarked SQL queries, which can be exploited to e.g. trick other users into executing unintended bookmarked SQL queries.
Successful exploitation requires that the bookmarks functionality is enabled and the configuration storage is set up and enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>712</id>
		<date>2011-02-13</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>opera</package>
		<vulnerable>10.10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>11.01-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4417</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0450
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0681
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0682
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0683
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0684
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0685
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0686
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0687</cve>
		<desc>Two weaknesses and some vulnerabilities have been reported in Opera, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions, disclose potentially sensitive information, and compromise a user's system.
			1) An integer truncation error when processing certain specially crafted HTML pages can be exploited by e.g. tricking a user into visiting a malicious website.
			2) The application allows users to perform certain actions via "opera:" URLs. This can be exploited to e.g. change certain configuration settings by tricking a user into clicking a specially crafted link via clickjacking.
			3) An error when processing certain HTTP responses or redirects can be exploited to bypass certain security restrictions and e.g. disclose the content of local files by loading them as a web resource.
			4) An error can cause Opera to launch the wrong executable in order to open a folder containing a downloaded file, which can lead to a malicious executable being launched.
			Successful exploitation of this weakness requires significant user interaction and only affects the Windows platform.
			5) The "Clear all email account passwords" option does not clear the email passwords unless the application is restarted, which can be exploited to gain access to the email accounts.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>711</id>
		<date>2011-02-13</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-mollom</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_1.13-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_1.14-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4321</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/912412</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in the Mollom module for Drupal, which may lead to exposure of sensitive information.
			The security issue is caused due to an error in the module which can lead to certain sensitive user data e.g. a user's password in clear text being logged via calls to Drupal's watchdog API.
			Successful exploitation requires that an attacker has "access site reports" permissions or has access to system syslog files.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>710</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.2-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.3-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4410</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4538
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0444
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-0445</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) A boundary error in the "dissect_enttec_dmx_data()" function (epan/dissectors/packet-enttec.c) when processing RLE Compressed DMX data of the ENTTEC protocol can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow via a specially crafted packet sent to UDP port 3333.
			2) A boundary error in the MAC-LTE dissector (epan/dissectors/packet-mac-lte.c) can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow.
			3) A boundary error in the "snmp_usm_password_to_key_sha1()" function (asn1/snmp/packet-snmp-template.c) can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow.
			Successful exploitation of vulnerabilities #1, #2, and #3 may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			4) An error in the ASN.1 BER dissector can be exploited to corrupt memory and cause the process to terminate.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>709</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>horde-webmail</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.9-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4408</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://lists.horde.org/archives/announce/2010/000574.html</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in various Horde products, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user while viewing a vCard. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious vCard is being viewed.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>708</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.3-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.4-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4399</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4536</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Certain input containing protocol strings (e.g. the HREF attribute of the "A" HTML tag) is not properly sanitised in the KSES library before being used. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in the context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>707</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-image</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_1.0_alpha4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_1.1-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4396</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see
			http://drupal.org/node/1005578</cve>
		<desc>See FSA706.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>706</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal-image</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_1.9-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_2.0-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4395</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see
			http://drupal.org/node/1005578</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Image module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in the context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>705</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-views</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_2.11-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_2.12-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4390</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see
			http://drupal.org/node/999380.</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in the Views module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Input passed via the URL is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>704</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mantis</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.3-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.4-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4389</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4348
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4349
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4350</cve>
		<desc>Gjoko Krstic has reported some vulnerabilities in MantisBT, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and disclose sensitive information.
			1) Input passed via the "db_type" parameter to admin/upgrade_unattended.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			2) Input passed via the "db_type" parameter to admin/upgrade_unattended.php is not properly verified before being used to include files. This can be exploited to include arbitrary file from local resources via directory traversal sequences and URL-encoded NULL bytes.
			NOTE: Successful exploitation requires that installation best-practices have not been followed and the "admin" directory has not been deleted after a successful installation.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>703</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.2-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.3-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4387</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://wordpress.org/news/2010/12/wordpress-3-0-3/</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The security issue is caused due to the XML-RPC remote publishing interface not properly enforcing access control restrictions for editing, publishing, or deleting posts.
			Successful exploitation of this security issue requires "Author level" or "Contributor level" permissions and that remote publishing is enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>702</id>
		<date>2010-12-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.2-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4382</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4257</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct SQL injection attacks.
			Input passed via the "Send Trackbacks" field when creating a new post is not properly sanitised in wp-includes/comment.php before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires "Author-level" permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>701</id>
		<date>2010-12-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.35-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.35-2haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4384</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3848
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3849
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3850</cve>
		<desc>This fixes multiple vulnerabilities, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions, cause a DoS (Denial of Service), and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>700</id>
		<date>2010-12-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.35-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.35-2haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4304</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2240
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2803
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2963
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3904</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in the Linux kernel:
			1) The do_anonymous_page function in mm/memory.c does not properly separate the stack and the heap, which allows context-dependent attackers to execute arbitrary code by writing to the bottom page of a shared memory segment, as demonstrated by a memory-exhaustion attack against the X.Org X server.
			2) The drm_ioctl function in drivers/gpu/drm/drm_drv.c in the Direct Rendering Manager (DRM) subsystem allows local users to obtain potentially sensitive information from kernel memory by requesting a large memory-allocation amount.
			3) drivers/media/video/v4l2-compat-ioctl32.c in the Video4Linux (V4L) implementation on 64-bit platforms does not validate the destination of a memory copy operation, which allows local users to write to arbitrary kernel memory locations, and consequently gain privileges, via a VIDIOCSTUNER ioctl call on a /dev/video device, followed by a VIDIOCSMICROCODE ioctl call on this device.
			4) The rds_page_copy_user function in net/rds/page.c in the Reliable Datagram Sockets (RDS) protocol implementation  does not properly validate addresses obtained from user space, which allows local users to gain privileges via crafted use of the sendmsg and recvmsg system calls.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>699</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>3.3.7-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.3.8.1-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4381</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4329</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Phpmyadmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to perform an XSS attack. See http://www.phpmyadmin.net/home_page/security/PMASA-2010-8.php for details.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>698</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.1-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.2-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4380</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4300
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4301</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) A boundary error in "dissect_ldss_transfer()" in epan/dissectors/packet-ldss.c can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
			2) An error in the ZigBee ZCL Discover Attribute Response dissector can be exploited to cause an infinite loop.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>697</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.1-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.2-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4380</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=2010-3445</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an infinite recursion error in the "dissect_unknown_ber()" function in epan/dissectors/packet-ber.c and can be exploited to cause a stack overflow e.g. via a specially crafted SNMP packet.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>696</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-lightbox2</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_1.9-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_1.10-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4326</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/919610.</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in Lightbox2 module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions and conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) A vulnerability exists in the access control mechanism for video content and can be exploited to get access to restricted video content.
			2) Input passed via unspecified parameters is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>695</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mantis</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.3-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4318</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3070
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3303
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3763</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in MantisBT, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks and by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) The application bundles a vulnerable version of NuSOAP.
			2) Certain Input passed via custom field types is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires "Manage Custom Fields" permissions.
			3) Certain input passed via project and category names is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user in print_all_bug_page_word.php. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires "Project Manager" permissions.
			4) Input passed via the Summary field when creating an issue is not properly sanitised before being used in core/summary_api.php. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires "Reporter" permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>694</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>3.3.7-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.3.8.1-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4381</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3263</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Certain unspecified input passed to the setup script is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			NOTE: Successful exploitation requires that installation best-practices have not been followed and the setup scripts have not been deleted after a successful installation.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>693</id>
		<date>2010-08-29</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>openoffice.org</package>
		<vulnerable>3.2.1-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.2.1-5haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4296</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2935
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2936</cve>
		<desc>Charlie Miller has discovered two vulnerabilities in OpenOffice.org Impress, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
		1) An integer truncation error when parsing certain content can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted file.
		2) A short integer overflow error when parsing certain content can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted file.
		Successful exploitation of the vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>692</id>
		<date>2010-08-29</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>3.3.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.3.5.1-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4294</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3056</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) Input passed via the "field_str" parameter to db_search.php , the "delimiter" parameter to db_sql.php, the "sort" parameter to db_structure.php, the "db" parameter to js/messages.php, the "sort_by" parameter to server_databases.php, the "checkprivs", "dbname", "pred_tablename", "selected_usr[]", "tablename", and "username" parameters to server_privileges.php, the "DefaultLang" parameter to setup/config.php, the "cpurge", "goto", "purge", "purgekey", "table", and "zero_rows" parameters to sql.php, and the "fields[multi_edit][]" parameter to tbl_replace.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			2) Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
