<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- if you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - xmllint is your friend
-->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>317</id>
		<date>2007-11-17</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>koffice</package>
		<vulnerable>1.6.3-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.6.3-3sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2559</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5392
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5393</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in KOffice, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system. The vulnerabilities are caused due to the use of vulnerable Xpdf code. For more information: FSA-316</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>316</id>
		<date>2007-11-17</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>xpdf</package>
		<vulnerable>3.02-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.02-4sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2558</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5392
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5393</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered some vulnerabilities in Xpdf, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) An array indexing error within the "DCTStream::readProgressiveDataUnit()" method in xpdf/Stream.cc can be exploited to corrupt memory via a specially crafted PDF file.
			2) An integer overflow error within the "DCTStream::reset()" method in xpdf/Stream.cc can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted PDF file.
			3) A boundary error within the "CCITTFaxStream::lookChar()" method in xpdf/Stream.cc can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by tricking a user into opening a PDF file containing a specially crafted "CCITTFaxDecode" filter.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>315</id>
		<date>2007-11-12</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.22-7sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.22-7sayshell2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2562</bts>
		<cve>CVE-2007-4997</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an off-by-two error within the function "ieee80211_rx()" in net/ieee80211/ieee80211_rx.c. This can be exploited to cause a kernel panic by sending a specially crafted ieee80211 frame with the IEEE80211_STYPE_QOS_DATA flag set to an affected system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>314</id>
		<date>2007-11-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>liferea</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.23-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.23-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2544</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5751</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in Liferea, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose sensitive information.
			The security issue is caused due to incorrect file permissions being set for the "feedlist.opml" backup file. This can be exploited to retrieve feed or proxy authentication usernames and passwords.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>313</id>
		<date>2007-11-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>django</package>
		<vulnerable>0.96-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.96-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2543</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5712</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Django, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to the Django internationalization system ("i18n") incorrectly processing HTTP headers. This can be exploited to allocate large amounts of memory by sending specially crafted HTTP "Accept-Language" requests.	Successful exploitation requires that the "USE_I18N" option and the "i18n" middleware component are enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>312</id>
		<date>2007-11-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>cups</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.2-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2540</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4351</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered a vulnerability in CUPS, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the "ippReadIO()" function in cups/ipp.c when processing IPP (Internet Printing Protocol) tags. This can be exploited to overwrite one byte on the stack with a zero by sending an IPP request containing specially crafted "textWithLanguage" or "nameWithLanguage" tags. Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>311</id>
		<date>2007-11-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.3.1-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2535</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5710</cve>
		<desc>Janek Vind has discovered a vulnerability in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Input passed to the "posts_columns" parameter in wp-admin/edit-post-rows.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site. Successful exploitation requires that "register_globals" is enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>310</id>
		<date>2007-11-01</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.22-6</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.22-7sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2455</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3731</cve>
		<desc>Evan Teran has reported a security issue in the Linux kernel, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in ptrace when single-stepping a debugged child process with invalid values in the "CS" register, which can be exploited to cause a kernel oops.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>309</id>
		<date>2007-10-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>asterisk-addons</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.4-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2506</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5488</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Asterisk-Addons, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct SQL injection attacks.
			Input passed via the source and destination numbers are not properly sanitised in the "cdr_addon_mysql" module before being used in an SQL query. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>308</id>
		<date>2007-10-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>asterisk</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.11-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.13-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2494</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5358</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Asterisk, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the IMAP-specific code for processing voicemail messages. This can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow via a specially crafted voicemail message sent as email containing an overly long (more than 1024 characters) combination of Content-Type or Content-Description headers.
			Successful exploitation requires that a user listens to the voicemail message via a phone.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>307</id>
		<date>2007-10-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>tomboy</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.0-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2370</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>Jab Oravec has reported a security issue in Tomboy, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused due to the "/usr/bin/tomboy" script incorrectly setting the environment variable LD_LIBRARY_PATH. This can be exploited to gain escalated privileges by e.g. tricking a user into running Tomboy in a directory containing a malicious library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>306</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>seamonkey</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.5-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2514</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1095
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2292
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4841
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5334
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5337
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5338
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5340</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities and a weakness have been reported in Mozilla SeaMonkey, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information, conduct phishing attacks, manipulate certain data, and potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) Various errors in the browser engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption.
			2) Various errors in the Javascript engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			3) An error in the handling of onUnload events can be exploited to read and manipulate the document's location of new pages.
			4) Input passed to the user ID when making an HTTP request using Digest Authentication is not properly sanitised before being used in a request. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTTP headers into a user's request when a proxy is used.
			5) An error when displaying web pages written in the XUL markup language can be exploited to hide the window's title bar and facilitate phishing attacks.
			6) An error exists in the handling of "smb:" and "sftp:" URI schemes on Linux systems with gnome-vfs support. This can be exploited to read any file owned by the target user via a specially crafted page on the same server. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has write access to a mutually accessible location on the target server and the user is tricked into loading the malicious page.
			7) An unspecified error in the handling of "XPCNativeWrappers" can lead to execution of arbitrary Javascript code with the user's privileges via subsequent access by the browser chrome (e.g. when a user right-clicks to open a context menu).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>305</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.8-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2235
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2513</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1095
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2292
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4841
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5334
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5337
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5338
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5340
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3511</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities and a weakness have been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information, conduct phishing attacks, manipulate certain data, and potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) Various errors in the browser engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption.
			2) Various errors in the Javascript engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			3) An error in the handling of onUnload events can be exploited to read and manipulate the document's location of new pages.
			4) Input passed to the user ID when making an HTTP request using Digest Authentication is not properly sanitised before being used in a request. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTTP headers into a user's request when a proxy is used.
			5) An error when displaying web pages written in the XUL markup language can be exploited to hide the window's title bar and facilitate phishing attacks.
			6) An error exists in the handling of "smb:" and "sftp:" URI schemes on Linux systems with gnome-vfs support. This can be exploited to read any file owned by the target user via a specially crafted page on the same server. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has write access to a mutually accessible location on the target server and the user is tricked into loading the malicious page.
			7) An unspecified error in the handling of "XPCNativeWrappers" can lead to execution of arbitrary Javascript code with the user's privileges via subsequent access by the browser chrome (e.g. when a user right-clicks to open a context menu).
			Furthermore a weakness has been discovered in Firefox, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information.
			The weakness is caused due to a design error within the focus handling of form fields and can potentially be exploited by changing the focus from a "textarea" field to a "file upload" form field via the "OnKeyDown" event.
			Successful exploitation allows an arbitrary file on the user's system to be uploaded to a malicious web site, but requires that the user is tricked into typing the file name into a "textarea" input form.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>304</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>drupal</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2507</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5595
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5596
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5597
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5593
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5594</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and bypass certain security restrictions, and by malicious users to conduct HTTP response splitting attacks.
			1) Input passed to unspecified parameters is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTTP headers, which is included in a response sent to the user. This allows arbitrary HTML and script code to be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires valid user credentials.
			2) The Upload module includes the ".html" file extension in its default whitelist for file uploads. This can be exploited to upload arbitrary HTML files and enticing users to visit them, thereby executing arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			3) The hook_components API operation does not pass the publication status. This makes it possible for modules including Organic groups and Subscriptions to send e-mail messages containing unpublished comments.
			Furthermore vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site request forgery attacks and to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) Input passed to unspecified parameters in install.php is not properly sanitised. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary code. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires that the configured SQL server is not reachable.
			2) A vulnerability is caused due to the application allowing users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any validity checks to verify the request. This can be exploited to delete users by enticing a logged-in administrator to visit a malicious site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>303</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>opera</package>
		<vulnerable>9.23-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.24-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2502</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5540
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5541</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Opera, where one vulnerability has an unknown impact and others can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and to compromise a user's system.
			1) Opera may launch external email or newsgroup clients incorrectly. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary commands by e.g. visiting a malicious website. Successful exploitation requires that the user has configured an external email or newsgroup client.
			2) An error when processing frames from different websites can be exploited to bypass the same-origin policy. This allows to overwrite functions of those frames and to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of other sites.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>302</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>hplip</package>
		<vulnerable>2.7.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.7.7-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2496</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5208</cve>
		<desc>Kees Cook has reported a vulnerability in HPLIP, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the hpssd daemon not properly sanitising certain input before using it to invoke sendmail using the "popen3()" method. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary commands with escalated privileges (e.g. "root") by sending specially crafted requests to the hpssd daemon.
			NOTE: Depending upon the configuration of hpssd, this may also be remotely exploitable.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>301</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>madwifi</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.3.2-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.3.3-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2495</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5448</cve>
		<desc>Clemens Kolbitsch and Sylvester Keil have reported a vulnerability in MadWifi, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the processing of beacon frames. This can be exploited via a specially crafted beacon frame with an overly large "length" value (greater than 15) in the extended supported rates element ("xrates").
			Successful exploitation causes the driver to exit and results in a kernel panic.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>300</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.11.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.11.1.2-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2489
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2503</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5386</cve>
		<desc>Omer Singer has reported two vulnerabilities in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) Input passed via the URL is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site. Successful exploitation requires that the user is running a browser that has not URL-encoded the request (e.g. Internet Explorer 6).
			2) Input passed in the URL to server_status.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site. Successful exploitation requires that the target user has valid user credentials. NOTE: Some other potential cross-site scripting problems have also been fixed by the vendor.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>299</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openssl</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.8-9</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.8-10sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2488</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4995</cve>
		<desc>Andy Polyakov has reported a vulnerability in OpenSSL, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an unspecified error within the DTLS implementation. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code.
			Note: Reportedly, this vulnerability affects only clients and servers explicitly using DTLS.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>298</id>
		<date>2007-10-19</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>pwlib</package>
		<vulnerable>1.10.10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.10.10-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2491</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4897</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in PWLib, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the "PString::vsprintf()" method in src/ptlib/common/contain.cxx. This can be exploited to cause a memory corruption by e.g. tricking an application using the library to use this function with a string longer than 1000 bytes.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>297</id>
		<date>2007-10-19</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wesnoth</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.6-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2486</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3917</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Wesnoth, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an unspecified error in the processing of UTF-8 strings within the multiplayer engine . This can be exploited by malicious clients to crash a vulnerable Wesnoth client.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>296</id>
		<date>2007-10-19</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libpng</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.20-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.22-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2475</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5267
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5266
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5268
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5269</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in libpng, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) Certain errors within libpng, including a logical NOT instead of a bitwise NOT in pngtrtran.c, an error in the 16bit cheap transparency extension, and an incorrect use of sizeof() may be exploited to crash an application using the library.
			2) Various out-of-bounds read errors exist within the functions "png_handle_pCAL()", "png_handle_sCAL()", "png_push_read_tEXt()", "png_handle_iTXt()", and "png_handle_ztXt()", which may be exploited by exploited to crash an application using the library.
			3) The vulnerability is caused due to an off-by-one error within the ICC profile chunk handling, which potentially can be exploited to crash an application using the library.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
