<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author?, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- If you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - read /hooks/README! -->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>621</id>
		<date>2009-09-27</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal</package>
		<vulnerable>5.19-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.20-1getorin1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3947</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/579484.</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to hijack accounts and compromise a vulnerable system, and by malicious people to conduct cross-site request forgery attacks.
			1) The OpenID module allows users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any validation checks to verify the requests. This can be exploited to e.g. add OpenID identities to existing accounts.
			2) An unspecified error within the OpenID Authentication 2.0 implementation can be exploited to hijack another user's account if the same OpenID 2.0 provider is used.
			3) An error within the File API when processing certain file extensions can be exploited to e.g. upload files which can be executed by the web server.
			Note: Successful exploitation requires that the web server is configured to ignore Drupal's ".htaccess" file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>620</id>
		<date>2009-09-27</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal-date</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_2.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_2.8-1getorin1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3951</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/579144.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Date module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being displayed in the page title. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation requires privileges to post date content.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>619</id>
		<date>2009-09-27</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>horde-webmail</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.4-1getorin1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3958</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3236</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Horde Groupware and Horde Groupware Webmail Edition, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting and script insertion attacks and by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) Two vulnerabilities can be exploited to conduct cross-site scripting or script insertion attacks.
			2) An error within the form library of the Horde Application Framework when handling image form fields can be exploited to overwrite arbitrary local files.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>618</id>
		<date>2009-09-27</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.2-1getorin1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3957</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3241
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3242
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3243</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) An error in the "OpcUa" dissector can be exploited to exhaust CPU and memory resources via a specially crafted "Service CallRequest" packet.
			2) An assertion error in the "GSM A RR" dissector can be exploited to cause a crash.
			3) An error in the TLS dissector can be exploited to cause a crash on certain platforms (e.g. Windows) via specially crafted TLS 1.2 network packets.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>617</id>
		<date>2009-09-27</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-devel</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_1.17-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_1.18-1getorin1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3964</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/585952.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Devel module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			The variable editor does not properly sanitise the variable name before displaying it to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
