<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author?, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- If you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - read /hooks/README! -->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>645</id>
		<date>2010-03-28</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal-mimemail</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_1.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_1.1-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4159</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/751934.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Mime Mail module for Drupal, while can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the PCRE regular expression engine, which can be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code.
			Successful exploitation requires the ability to send HTML email via the Mime Mail module.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>644</id>
		<date>2010-03-23</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>3.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.6.2-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4158</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1028</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow error when processing WOFF fonts. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a web page embedding a WOFF font with an overly large "origLen" field.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>643</id>
		<date>2010-03-16</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>libesmtp</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.4-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4141</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-2408</cve>
		<desc>libesmtp did not properly handle a '\0' character in a domain name in the subject's Common Name (CN) field of an X.509 certificate, which allows man-in-the-middle attackers to spoof arbitrary SSL servers via a crafted certificate issued by a legitimate Certification Authority.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>642</id>
		<date>2010-03-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-i18n</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_1.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_1.3-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4134</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/731632.</cve>
		<desc>See FSA641 for details.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>641</id>
		<date>2010-03-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal-i18n</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_2.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_2.6-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4134</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/731632.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Internationalization module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being used to translate the text. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code by passing a malicious string to the input filter.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>640</id>
		<date>2010-03-11</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6</package>
		<vulnerable>6.15-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.16-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4133</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/731710.</cve>
		<desc>See FSA639 for details.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>639</id>
		<date>2010-03-11</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal</package>
		<vulnerable>5.21-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.22-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4132</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://drupal.org/node/731710.</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks and bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) Input passed via the "langcode", "name", and "native" parameters in the languages interface while using the Locale module is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation requires "administer languages" permissions.
			2) An error in the handling of certain sessions can be exploited to maintain an open session despite the user being blocked.
</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>638</id>
		<date>2010-03-10</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>2.9.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.9.2-1locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4131</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0682</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The vulnerability is caused due to WordPress not properly restricting access to trashed posts, which can be exploited to e.g. view a trashed post by accessing it's page directly.
			Successful exploitation requires a valid user account.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>637</id>
		<date>2010-03-09</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>xar</package>
		<vulnerable>1.5.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.5.2-2locris1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4128</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0055</cve>
		<desc>Braden Thomas from Apple has discovered a signature verification bypass issue in xar.  The issue is that xar_open assumes that the checksum is stored at offset 0, but xar_signature_copy_signed_data uses xar property "checksum/offset" to find the offset to the checksum when validating the signature.  As a result, a modified xar archive can pass signature validation by putting the checksum for the modified TOC at offset 0, pointing "checksum/offset" at the non-modified checksum at a higher offset, and using the original non-modified signature.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
