<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author?, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- If you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - read /hooks/README! -->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>450</id>
		<date>2008-06-13</date>
		<package>imlib2</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.0-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3124</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2426</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered two vulnerabilities in imlib2, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or compromise an application using the library.
			1) A boundary error exists within the "load()" function in src/modules/loaders/loader_pnm.c when processing the header of a PNM image file. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted PNM image in an application using the imlib2 library.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.
			2) A boundary error exists within the "load()" function in src/modules/loader_xpm.c when processing an XPM image file. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted XPM image in an application using the imlib2 library.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>469</id>
		<date>2008-06-13</date>
		<package>mrxvt</package>
		<vulnerable>0.5.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.5.3-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3090</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in mrxvt, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			For more information, see FSA466.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>468</id>
		<date>2008-06-13</date>
		<package>rxvt-unicode</package>
		<vulnerable>9.02-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.02-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3089</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in rxvt-unicode, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			For more information, see FSA466.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>467</id>
		<date>2008-06-13</date>
		<package>aterm</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.1-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3088</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in aterm, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			For more information, see FSA466.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>466</id>
		<date>2008-06-13</date>
		<package>rxvt</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.4-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.7.10-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2925</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1142</cve>
		<desc>Bernhard R. Link has reported a security issue in rxvt, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused due to the program using ":0" as it's X11 display if the DISPLAY environment variable is missing. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the user running rxvt via a malicious X server.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>465</id>
		<date>2008-06-10</date>
		<package>net-snmp</package>
		<vulnerable>5.4.1-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.4.1-4kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3092</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2292</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Net-snmp, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the "__snprint_value()" function in perl/SNMP/SNMP.xs. This can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow in an application using the Net-snmp Perl module by tricking the user into connecting to a malicious SNMP agent.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>464</id>
		<date>2008-06-06</date>
		<package>horde-webmail</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.6-1kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3120</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6018</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered a vulnerability in IMP Webmail Client and Horde Groupware Webmail Edition, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions and manipulate data.
			The HTML filter does not filter out frame and frameset HTML elements. Additionally, the application allows users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any validity checks to verify the request. This can be exploited to (a) delete an arbitrary number of e-mail messages by referencing their numeric IDs and (b) purge deleted mails, when the victim opens a malicious HTML mail.
			Successful exploitation requires that the victim opens the HTML part of a malicious message.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>463</id>
		<date>2008-06-06</date>
		<package>openssl</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.8-11</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.8-12kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3114</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0891
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1672</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in OpenSSL, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) A double-free error in the handling of server name extension data if "server_name" set to 0x00 can be exploited to crash a server application using OpenSSL by sending a specially crafted TLS 1.0 Client Hello packet.
			Successful exploitation requires that OpenSSL is compiled using the TLS server name extensions.
			2) A NULL pointer dereference error can be exploited by a malicious server to crash a client application when the "Server Key exchange message" is omitted from a TLS handshake and anonymous Diffie-Hellman key exchange is used.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>462</id>
		<date>2008-05-26</date>
		<package>libxslt</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.22-2kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.22-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3104</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1767</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in libxslt, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the handling of XSL style-sheet files. This can potentially be exploited to trigger the use of uninitialized memory in e.g. a call to "free()" when a specially crafted XSL file is being processed by an application using the library.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>461</id>
		<date>2008-05-26</date>
		<package>mysql</package>
		<vulnerable>5.0.51-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.0.51-3kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3075</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2079</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in MySQL, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The problem is that it is possible to bypass certain privilege checks by creating a MyISAM table with certain DATA DIRECTORY and INDEX DIRECTORY options to overwrite existing table files in the MySQL data directory.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>460</id>
		<date>2008-05-26</date>
		<package>seamonkey</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.9-1kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.9-1kalgan2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3021</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1380</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Mozilla SeaMonkey, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system. For more information, see FSA431.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>459</id>
		<date>2008-05-26</date>
		<package>django</package>
		<vulnerable>0.96.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.96.2-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3084</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2302</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Django, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Input passed via the URL is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user through the login form. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>458</id>
		<date>2008-05-26</date>
		<package>asterisk</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.17-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.19.2-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3077</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1897
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1923</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Asterisk, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to improper verification of ACK responses during IAX2 handshakes, which can be exploited to spoof an IAX2 handshake and cause a DoS via high bandwidth usage.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>457</id>
		<date>2008-05-25</date>
		<package>kvm</package>
		<vulnerable>61-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>61-3kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3044</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2004</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in KVM, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions or cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The error can be exploited by a guest to read arbitrary files on the host via a specially crafted disk header. For more information, see FSA455.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>456</id>
		<date>2008-05-25</date>
		<package>xemacs</package>
		<vulnerable>21.4.21-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>21.4.21-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3041</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1694</cve>
		<desc>Some security issues have been reported in XEmacs, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to perform certain actions with escalated privileges.
			The security issues are caused due to the use of vulnerable GNU Emacs code. For more information, see FSA423.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>455</id>
		<date>2008-05-25</date>
		<package>qemu</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.1-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.1-3kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3043</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2004</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in QEMU, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the "drive_init()" function in vl.c determining the format of a disk from data contained in the disk's header. This can be exploited by a malicious user in a guest system to e.g. read arbitrary files on the host by writing a fake header to a raw formatted disk image.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>454</id>
		<date>2008-05-25</date>
		<package>chicken</package>
		<vulnerable>2.732-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.1.10-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3091</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0674</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability been reported in Chicken, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to the use of a vulnerable version of the PCRE library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>453</id>
		<date>2008-05-25</date>
		<package>gnutls</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.2.5-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3100</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1948
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1949
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1950</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in GnuTLS, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to potentially compromise an application using the library.
			1) A boundary error exists in the processing "Client Hello" messages containing a "Server Name" extension. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted TLS packet.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			2) A NULL-pointer dereference error in the processing of TLS packets containing multiple "Client Hello" messages can be exploited to crash an affected application.
			3) A signedness error exists within the "_gnutls_ciphertext2compressed()" function in lib/gnutls_cipher.c. This can be exploited to cause an out of bounds read and crash an affected application via specially crafted, encrypted TLS data.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>452</id>
		<date>2008-05-20</date>
		<package>graphicsmagick</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.11-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.12-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3076</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue, see http://sourceforge.net/project/shownotes.php?release_id=595544</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in GraphicsMagick, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The security issue is caused due to the improper processing of file extensions and can be exploited to e.g. access X11 or to invoke certain delegate programs.
			Successful exploitation requires that a user is tricked into processing a malicious file with a specific file extension.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>451</id>
		<date>2008-05-20</date>
		<package>audacity</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.3-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.5-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3080</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6061</cve>
		<desc>Viktor Griph has reported a security issue in Audacity, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to delete arbitrary files and directories.
			The security issue is caused due to the "AudacityApp::OnInit()" method in src/AudacityApp.cpp handling temporary files in an insecure manner. This can be exploited to delete arbitrary files and directories via symlink attacks, or to cause a deadlock.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>450</id>
		<date>2008-05-20</date>
		<package>pngcrush</package>
		<vulnerable>1.6.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.6.5-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3079</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1382</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Pngcrush, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose potentially sensitive information or potentially compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the use of vulnerable libpng code. For more information, see FSA434.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>449</id>
		<date>2008-05-20</date>
		<package>rdesktop</package>
		<vulnerable>1.5.0-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.6.0-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3078</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1801
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1802
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1803</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in rdesktop, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) An integer underflow error in iso.c when processing RDP requests can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
			2) An input validation error in rdp.c when processing RDP redirect requests can be exploited to cause a BSS-based buffer overflow.
			3) A signedness error within "xrealloc()" in rdesktop.c can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code but requires that a user is tricked into connecting to a malicious RDP server.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>448</id>
		<date>2008-05-20</date>
		<package>php</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2.5-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2.6-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3074</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0599
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2050
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2051
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2107
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2108</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in PHP, where some have unknown impacts and others can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions, and potentially by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) An unspecified error in the FastCGI SAPI can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow.
			2) An error in the processing of multibyte characters within the "escapeshellcmd()" and "escapeshellarg()" functions can be exploited to escape the inserted backslash or quote characters via certain multibyte characters.
			Successful exploitation allows to bypass the "safe_mode_exec_dir" and "disable_functions" directives, and potentially to inject arbitrary shell commands via user controlled input, but requires that the shell uses a locale with a variable width character (e.g. GBK, EUC-KR, SJIS).
			3) A vulnerability is caused due to an error during path translation in cgi_main.c. This can potentially be exploited to execute arbitrary code, but depends on how a targeted application is using PHP.
			4) An error in cURL can be exploited to bypass the "safe_mode" directive.
			5) A boundary error in PCRE can potentially be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS or compromise a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>447</id>
		<date>2008-05-15</date>
		<package>eterm</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.4-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.4-3kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2918</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1692</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in Eterm, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges. Eterm 0.9.4 opens a terminal window on :0 if -display is not specified and the DISPLAY environment variable is not set, which might allow local users to hijack X11 connections. NOTE: realistic attack scenarios require that the victim enters a command on the wrong machine.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>446</id>
		<date>2008-05-15</date>
		<package>kdelibs</package>
		<vulnerable>3.5.9-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.5.9-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3047</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1671</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in KDE, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to potentially gain escalated privileges.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the start_kdeinit script (installed setuid root by default). This can be exploited to send signals to privileged processes, cause a DoS, or potentially execute arbitrary code in the context of the target process.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>445</id>
		<date>2008-05-15</date>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.24-4kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.24-4kalgan2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3060</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1669</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Linux kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error when preventing race conditions between "fcntl_setlk()" and "close()" calls on SMP systems. This can be exploited to trigger the improper, reordered access to the file descriptor table and the "file_lock" structure of an inode, between threads running on different CPUs.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>444</id>
		<date>2008-05-15</date>
		<package>thunderbird</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.12-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.14-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2906</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1233
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1234
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1235
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1236
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1237</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mozilla Thunderbird, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions, conduct cross-site scripting attacks, or potentially compromise a user's system. For more information, see FSA407.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>443</id>
		<date>2008-05-15</date>
		<package>util-linux-ng</package>
		<vulnerable>2.13.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.13.1-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3046</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1926</cve>
		<desc>A weakness has been reported in util-linux-ng, which can be exploited by malicious people to manipulate certain data.
			The security issue is caused due to an error in login.c while logging login attempts. This can be exploited to inject e.g. an arbitrary address in the audit logs via a specially crafted username.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>442</id>
		<date>2008-05-15</date>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>2.3.3-2kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.5.1-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3048</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1930
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-2068</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks, bypass certain security restrictions, and to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) A vulnerability is caused due to improper access restriction of the administration section. This can be exploited to bypass the authentication mechanism and gain administrative access by setting a specially crafted cookie. This can further be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires that registering new accounts is enabled.
			The vulnerability is reported in version 2.5.
			2) Input passed to an unspecified parameter is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>441</id>
		<date>2008-05-05</date>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.24-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.24-4kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3050</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1375</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Linux kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to potentially gain escalated privileges.
			A race condition error exists in the dnotify subsystem between calls to "fcntl()" and "close()". This can be exploited to cause a system crash or potentially gain root privileges.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>440</id>
		<date>2008-05-05</date>
		<package>frugalwareutils</package>
		<vulnerable>0.7.9-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.7.9-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3052</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in frugalwareutils, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS on a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to creating new files as root without checking the current value of umask.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>439</id>
		<date>2008-05-05</date>
		<package>vorbis-tools</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.1-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.1-4kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3032</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1686</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in vorbis-tools, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the use of vulnerable libfishsound; an input validation error when processing Speex headers, which can be exploited via a specially crafted Speex stream containing a negative "modeID" field in the header.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>438</id>
		<date>2008-05-05</date>
		<package>xine-lib</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.11-1kalgan2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.11-1kalgan3</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3027</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1878</cve>
		<desc>Guido Landi has discovered a vulnerability in xine-lib, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the "demux_nsf_send_chunk()" function in src/demuxers/demux_nsf.c. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow via an overly long NSF title.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>437</id>
		<date>2008-05-05</date>
		<package>xine-lib</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.11-1kalgan2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.11-1kalgan3</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3010</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1686</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in xine-lib, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the use of vulnerable libfishsound; an input validation error when processing Speex headers, which can be exploited via a specially crafted Speex stream containing a negative "modeID" field in the header.
		
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>436</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.11.5.1-1kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.11.5.2-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3035</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1924</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious users to disclose sensitive information.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an unspecified error and can be exploited to disclose arbitrary files via a specially crafted HTTP POST request.
			Successful exploitation requires a certain level of access e.g. on a shared host.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>435</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>openssh</package>
		<vulnerable>4.7p1-4kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.7p1-4kalgan2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2961</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1657</cve>
		<desc>A weakness has been reported in OpenSSH, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The weakness is caused due to the improper implementation of the "ForceCommand" directive. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary commands via the ~/.ssh/rc file even if a "ForceCommand" directive is in effect.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>434</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>libpng</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.24-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.24-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3013</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1382</cve>
		<desc>Tavis Ormandy has reported a vulnerability in libpng, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service), disclose potentially sensitive information, or potentially compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the improper handling of PNG chunks unknown to the library. This can be exploited to trigger the use of uninitialized memory in e.g. a "free()" call via unknown PNG chunks having a length of zero.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code, but requires that the application calls the "png_set_read_user_chunk_fn()" function or the "png_set_keep_unknown_chunks()" function under specific conditions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>433</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>cups</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.6-2kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.6-2kalgan2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3012</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1722</cve>
		<desc>Thomas Pollet has reported a vulnerability in CUPS, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to two integer overflow errors in filter/image-png.c when processing PNG files. These can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via overly large width and height PNG fields.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>432</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>clamav</package>
		<vulnerable>0.92.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.93-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3014</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1100
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0314
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1387
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1833
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1835
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1836
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1837</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in ClamAV, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions, to cause a DoS (Denial of Service), or to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) A boundary error exists within the "cli_scanpe()" function in libclamav/pe.c. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted "Upack" executable.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.
			2) A boundary error within the processing of PeSpin packed executables in libclamav/spin.c can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			3) An unspecified error in the processing of ARJ files can be exploited to hang ClamAV.
			4) A boundary error within the processing of WWPack packed PE files in libclamav/pe.c can be exploited to cause a heap corruption.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			5) An error in the processing of RAR files can be exploited to bypass the scanning mechanism via a RAR file containing an invalid version number.
			6) An error exists within the "rfc2231()" function in message.c. This can be exploited to trigger the return of strings that are not NULL terminated and cause a crash.
			7) An error in libclamunrar can be exploited to crash the application via specially crafted RAR files.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>431</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.13-1kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.14-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3022</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1380</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the Javascript Garbage Collector and can be exploited to cause a memory corruption via specially crafted Javascript code.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>430</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>sweep</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.2-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.2-3kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3025</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1686</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in sweep, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system. For more information, see FSA426.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>429</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>vlc</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.6-12kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.6-12kalgan2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3024</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1686</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in vlc, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system. For more information, see FSA426.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>428</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>sdl_sound</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.1-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.1-5kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3026</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1686</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in sdl_sound, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system. For more information, see FSA426.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>427</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>gst-plugins-good</package>
		<vulnerable>0.10.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.10.7-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3031</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1686</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in gst-plugins-good, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system. For more information, see FSA426.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>426</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>speex</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2beta3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2beta3-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3023</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1686</cve>
		<desc>The reference speex decoder from the Speex library is performing insufficient boundary checks on a header structure read from user input.
			A user controlled field in the header structure is used to build a function pointer. The reference speex decoder does not check for negative values for the field, allowing the function pointer to be pointed at an arbitary position in memory. This allows remote code execution.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>425</id>
		<date>2008-04-25</date>
		<package>mailman</package>
		<vulnerable>2.1.9-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.1.9-3kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3020</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0564</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Mailman, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Certain input when editing the list templates and the list info attribute is not properly sanitised before being stored. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which is executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious website is accessed.
			Successful exploitation requires list administrator privileges.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>424</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<package>comix</package>
		<vulnerable>3.6.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.6.4-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2923</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1568</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Comix, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's sytem.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the improper verification of received filenames when executing the rar, unrar, or jpegtran programs. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary commands via a file containing shell metacharacters within the filename.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>423</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<package>emacs</package>
		<vulnerable>22.1-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>22.1-3kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3006</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1694</cve>
		<desc>Steve Grubb discovered that vcdiff script as shipped with Emacs uses temporary files insecurely, which makes it possible for local attacker to conduct a symlink attack and make the victim overwrite arbitrary file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>422</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<package>vlc</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.6-11</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.6-12kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2904</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0073
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1489</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in VLC Media Player, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) An integer overflow error within the "MP4_ReadBox_rdrf()" function in modules/demux/mp4/libmp4.c can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via e.g. a MP4 file with a specially crafted RDRF atom.
			2) A boundary error within the "sdpplin_parse()" function in modules/access/rtsp/real_sdpplin.c can be exploited to overwrite arbitrary memory regions.
			3) Two integer overflow errors within the "cinepak_decode_frame()" function in modules/codec/cinepak.c can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
			Successful exploitation of the vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>421</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<package>sdlimage</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.6-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2916</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6697
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0544</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in SDL_image, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise an application using the library.
			1) A boundary error within the "LWZReadByte()" function in IMG_gif.c can be exploited to trigger the overflow of a static buffer via a specially crafted GIF file.
			2) A boundary error within the "IMG_LoadLBM_RW()" function in IMG_lbm.c can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted IFF ILBM file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>420</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<package>flashplugin</package>
		<vulnerable>9.0.115.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.0.124.0-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2959</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0071
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5275
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6019
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6243
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6637
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1654
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1655</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Adobe Flash Player, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions, conduct cross-site scripting attacks, or to potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) A boundary error exists in the processing of "Declare Function (V7)" tags. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via specially crafted flags.
			2) An integer overflow in the processing of multimedia files can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow.
			Successful exploitation of the vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			3) Errors when pinning a hostname to an IP address can be exploited to conduct DNS rebinding attacks.
			4) An error when sending HTTP headers can be exploited to bypass cross-domain policy files.
			5) An error exists in the enforcing of cross-domain policy files. This can be exploited to bypass certain security restrictions on web servers hosting cross-domain policy files.
			6) Input passed to unspecified parameters when handling e.g. the "asfunction:" protocol is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to inject arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>419</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<package>gnome-screensaver</package>
		<vulnerable>2.20.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.20.0-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2931</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6389
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0887</cve>
		<desc>A weakness and a security issue have been reported in gnome-screensaver, which can be exploited by malicious people with physical access to disclose potentially sensitive information or bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) A weakness is caused due to the "Leave message" feature allowing attackers to e.g. paste the contents of the clipboard of the user who's screen is currently locked, which can be exploited to disclose potentially sensitive information.
			2) A security issue is caused due to an error if the NIS authentication method is used. This can be exploited to bypass the authentication check and unlock the screen if the NIS server is not reachable.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>418</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<package>mtr</package>
		<vulnerable>0.72-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.73-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2956</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>David Leadbeater has reported a vulnerability in mtr, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to mtr not properly limiting the length of some buffers.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>417</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>xine-lib</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.11-1kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.11-1kalgan2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2892</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1482</cve>
		<desc>Luigi Auriemma has reported some vulnerabilities in xine-lib, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to integer overflow errors when allocating memory in src/demuxers/demux_flv.c, src/demuxers/demux_qt.c, src/demuxers/demux_real.c, src/demuxers/demux_wc3movie.c, src/demuxers/ebml.c, and src/demuxers/demux_film.c. These can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows via overly large fields included in e.g. FLV, MOV, RM, MVE, MKV, and CAK files.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>416</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>pdns-recursor</package>
		<vulnerable>3.1.4-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.1.5-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2924</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1637</cve>
		<desc>Amit Klein has reported a vulnerability in PowerDNS Recursor, which can be exploited by malicious people to poison the DNS cache.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the application using predictable standard C library functions to generate random numbers (e.g. "rand()" and "srand()"), which are then used to create the transaction ID (TRXID) and UDP source port. This can be exploited to poison the DNS cache by guessing the transaction TRXID and the UDP source port.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>415</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>m4</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.10-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2963</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1687
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1688</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability and a security issue have been reported in GNU M4, which can be exploited by malicious people to manipulate certain data or to potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) A format string error exists within the "produce_frozen_state()" function in src/freeze.c. This can be exploited via a specially crafted filename passed as a parameter to "m4 -F".
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code, but requires that the user is tricked into processing a filename containing malicious format specifiers.
			2) An error within the implementation of the "maketemp" and "mkstemp" macros can potentially be exploited to trigger the processing of improper files via special characters contained in the output string.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>414</id>
		<date>2008-04-14</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>lighttpd</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.19-1kalgan1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.19-1kalgan2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2922</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1531</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in lighttpd, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to lighttpd not properly clearing the OpenSSL error queue. This can be exploited to close concurrent SSL connections of lighttpd by terminating one SSL connection.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>413</id>
		<date>2008-04-12</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>python</package>
		<vulnerable>2.5.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.5.2-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2954</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1679</cve>
		<desc>David Remahl has discovered a security issue in the imageop module for Python, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The security issue is caused due to an incomplete fix (see FSA295) and can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow when specially crafted parameters are passed to the function.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>412</id>
		<date>2008-04-12</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>cups</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.6-2kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2962</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0047
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1373</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in CUPS, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) A boundary error exists within the "cgiCompileSearch()" function in cgi-bin/search.c. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted IPP request.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code, but requires that the vulnerable system is sharing printers on the network.
			NOTE: If printer sharing is disabled, the vulnerability can only be exploited by malicious, local users.
			2) A boundary error exists within the "gif_read_image()" function in filter/image-gif.c. This can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow via overly large "code_size" values in GIF image files.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>411</id>
		<date>2008-04-12</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>opera</package>
		<vulnerable>9.26-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.27-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2930</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue, see:
			http://www.opera.com/support/search/view/881/
			http://www.opera.com/support/search/view/882/</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Opera, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) An error when prompting the user to add a newsfeed can be exploited to cause an invalid memory access via a specially crafted newsfeed source.
			2) An error exists in the processing of HTML CANVAS elements. This can be exploited to cause a memory corruption via specially crafted scaled pattern images.
			Successful exploitation of the vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>410</id>
		<date>2008-04-10</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>gnupg2</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.9-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2905</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1530</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in GnuPG, which can potentially be exploited to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error when importing keys with duplicated IDs. This can be exploited to cause a memory corruption when importing keys via --refresh-keys or --import.
			Successful exploitation potentially allows execution of arbitrary code, but has not been proven yet.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>409</id>
		<date>2008-04-10</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>gnupg</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.9-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2905</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1530</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in GnuPG, which can potentially be exploited to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error when importing keys with duplicated IDs. This can be exploited to cause a memory corruption when importing keys via --refresh-keys or --import.
			Successful exploitation potentially allows execution of arbitrary code, but has not been proven yet.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>408</id>
		<date>2008-04-04</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>0.99.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.0-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2915</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1561
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1562
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1563</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to errors in the X.509sat, Roofnet, LDAP, and SCCP dissectors. These can be exploited to cause the application to crash when processing specially crafted packets that are either captured off the wire or loaded via a capture file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>407</id>
		<date>2008-04-04</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>seamonkey</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.9-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2908</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4879
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1195
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1233
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1234
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1235
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1236
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1237
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1238
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1240
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1241</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities and weaknesses have been reported in Mozilla SeaMonkey, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions, disclose potentially sensitive information, conduct cross-site scripting and phishing attacks, and potentially compromise a user's system.
			For more information, please see FSA406.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>406</id>
		<date>2008-04-04</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.12-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.13-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2907</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4879
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1195
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1233
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1234
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1235
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1236
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1237
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1238
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1240
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1241</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities and weaknesses have been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions, disclose potentially sensitive information, conduct cross-site scripting and phishing attacks, and potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) An unspecified error in the handling of "XPCNativeWrappers" can lead to the execution of arbitrary Javascript code with the user's privileges via "setTimeout()" calls.
			2) Various errors in the handling of Javascript code can be exploited to conduct cross-site scripting attacks or execute arbitrary code.
			3) Various errors in the layout engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption.
			4) Various errors in the Javascript engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption.
			Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			5) An error within the handling of HTTP "Referer:" headers sent with requests to URLs containing "Basic Authentication" credentials having an empty username can be exploited to bypass cross-site request forgery protections.
			6) The problem is that Firefox offers a previously configured private SSL certificate when establishing connections to webservers requesting SSL Client Authentication. This can potentially be exploited to disclose sensitive information via a malicious webserver.
			7) An error in the handling of the "jar:" protocol can be exploited to establish connections to arbitrary ports on the local machine.
			8) An error when displaying XUL pop-up windows can be exploited to hide the window's borders and facilitate phishing attacks.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>405</id>
		<date>2008-04-01</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>openssh</package>
		<vulnerable>4.7p1-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.7p1-4kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2911</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1483</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in OpenSSH, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose sensitive information.
			The vulnerability is caused due to sshd improperly binding TCP ports on the local IPV6 interface if required ports on the IPV4 interface are in use. This can be exploited by a malicious, local user to intercept an X11 forwarding session by listening to a port used by sshd to forward the local X11 display (e.g. port 6010/TCP).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>404</id>
		<date>2008-04-01</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.11.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.11.5.1-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2917</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1567</cve>
		<desc>im Hermann has discovered a vulnerability in phpMyAdmin, which can potentially be exploited by malicious users to disclose sensitive information.
			The MySQL username, password, and the Blowfish secret key are stored as plain text in session files. This can potentially be exploited e.g. by users on shared hosts to access that information.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>403</id>
		<date>2008-04-01</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>horde-webmail</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.6-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2910</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1284</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in various Horde products, which can be exploited by malicious users to disclose sensitive information and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			Input passed to the "theme" parameter is not properly sanitised before being used. This can be exploited to include arbitrary files from local resources, using directory traversal attacks and URL-encoded NULL bytes ("%00").
			NOTE: Other attack vectors are also reported to exist.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code, but requires valid user credentials.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>402</id>
		<date>2008-04-01</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>mplayer</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0rc2-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0rc2-4kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2913</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1558</cve>
		<desc>k`sOSe has discovered a vulnerability in MPlayer, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow error in the "sdpplin_parse()" function in stream/realrtsp/sdpplin.c. This can be exploited to overwrite arbitrary memory regions via an overly large "StreamCount" SDP parameter.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>401</id>
		<date>2008-04-01</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>j2sdk</package>
		<vulnerable>6-7</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6-8kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2845</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1185
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1186
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1187
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1188
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1189
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1190
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1191
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1192
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1193
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1194
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1195
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1196</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Sun Java, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service), to bypass certain security restrictions, or to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) Two unspecified errors in the Java Runtime Environment Virtual Machine can be exploited by a malicious, untrusted applet to read and write local files and execute local applications.
			2) An unspecified error in the Java Runtime Environment (JRE) when processing XSLT transformations can be exploited by untrusted applets or applications to e.g. read certain URL resources or potentially execute arbitrary code.
			3) A boundary error exists in the "useEncodingDecl()" function when parsing the xml header character encoding attribute. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow and execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted JNLP file containing an overly long charset name in the xml header.
			4) A boundary error exists in the "useEncodingDecl()" function when processing xml-based JNLP files for UTF8 characters. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow and execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted JNLP file containing overly long key name in the xml header.
			5) A boundary error exist in Java Web Start, which can be exploited e.g. by an untrusted Java Web Start application to read and write local files and execute local applications.
			6) An unspecified error in Java Web Start can be exploited by a malicious, untrusted applet to read and write local files or execute local applications.
			7) An unspecified error in Java Web Start can be exploited by an untrusted Java Web Start application to create files on the system and run local applications with the privileges of the user running the untrusted Java Web Start application.
			8) An unspecified error in the Java Plug-in can be exploited by an applet to bypass the same origin policy and to execute local applications.
			9) Some errors in the Java Runtime Environment image parsing library within the processing of ICC profiles can be exploited to crash the JVM or to write local files and execute local applications.
			10) An error in the Java Runtime Environment may allow java script code within a browser to make connections through Java APIs to network services on the local system.
			11) A boundary error exists in Java Web Start in the processing of JNLP files, which can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow when a user visits a malicious web site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>400</id>
		<date>2008-03-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>bzip2</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.5-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2903</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1372</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in bzip2, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the handling of malformed archives and can potentially be exploited to cause a DoS.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>399</id>
		<date>2008-03-24</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>xine-lib</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.10.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.11-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2887</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0073</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered a vulnerability in xine-lib, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the "sdpplin_parse()" function in input/libreal/sdpplin.c. This can be exploited to overwrite arbitrary memory regions via an overly large "streamid" SDP parameter included in a malicious RTSP stream.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>398</id>
		<date>2008-03-24</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>tetex</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0-12</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0-13kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2592</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5935
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5936
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5937</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in teTeX, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose and manipulate sensitive information and by malicious people to potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) A boundary error in dvips can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow when a user is tricked into opening a specially crafted DVI file containing an overly long hypertext reference.
			Successful exploitation requires that dvips is invoked with the "-z" option.
			2) Some boundary errors in dviljk can be exploited to cause buffer overflows when a user is enticed to print a specially crafted DVI file.
			Successful exploitation of vulnerabilities #1 and #2 may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			3) An error due to dvips using the insecure "tmpnam()" function when converting DVI files can potentially be exploited to disclose and modify sensitive information.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>397</id>
		<date>2008-03-24</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>unzip</package>
		<vulnerable>5.52-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.52-5kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2886</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0888</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in UnZip, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the use of uninitialized pointers in the "inflate_dynamic()" function in inflate.c. This can potentially be exploited to free an attacker-controlled memory region and execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted ZIP compressed file.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>396</id>
		<date>2008-03-24</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>rails</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.6-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2591</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3227
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5379
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5380
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6077</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Ruby on Rails, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information and conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) Input passed to the "to_json" function is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			2) An error in ActiveResource when processing responses using the "Hash.from_xml" function can be exploited to determine the existence of files and to read the contents of arbitrary XML files.
			3) A security issue is caused due to lib/action_controller/cgi_process.rb removing the ":cookie_only" attribute from "DEFAULT_SESSION_OPTIONS" and can be exploited to conduct session fixation attacks against applications using the affected component.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>395</id>
		<date>2008-03-24</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>ghostscript</package>
		<vulnerable>8.61-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>8.62-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2823</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-0411</cve>
		<desc>Chris Evans has reported a vulnerability in Ghostscript, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the "zseticcspace()" function in zicc.c. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow via an overly large "Range" array.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>394</id>
		<date>2008-03-18</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>lighttpd</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.18-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.19-1kalgan1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2844</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1111
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-1270</cve>
		<desc>Some security issues have been reported in lighttpd, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose potentially sensitive information.
			1) A security issue is caused due to an error in mod_cgi, which can lead to the disclosure of source code when lighttpd is unable to fork.
			2) A security issue is caused due to the mod_userdir module using "$HOME" by default if no userdir.path is set. This can be exploited to disclose the content of arbitrary files on certain systems via e.g. the "nobody" user.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
