<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- if you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - xmllint is your friend
-->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>139</id>
		<date>2007-03-28</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.20-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.20-5terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1858</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1592</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) Listening IPv6 TCP sockets are incorrectly sharing the "ipv6_fl_socklist" IPv6 flowlist with child sockets. This can be exploited to e.g. cause a kernel crash by performing certain actions on IPv6 TCP sockets.
			2) The "hrtimer_forward()" does not correctly check for "timer->expires" overflows on 64bit machines. This can be exploited to cause a DoS by using very large timer values. Successful exploitation may require a 64bit machine and that high resolution timers are enabled.
			3) A NULL pointer dereference within the "do_ipv6_setsockopt()" function in net/ipv6/ipv6_sockglue.c can be exploited to cause a kernel crash by calling "setsockopt()" with malicious parameters.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>138</id>
		<date>2007-03-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>squid</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.STABLE10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.STABLE12-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1855</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1560</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Squid, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the processing of TRACE requests in squid/src/client_side.c. This can be exploited to crash the service via a specially crafted TRACE request.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>137</id>
		<date>2007-03-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.3-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1850</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue, see: http://www.mozilla.org/security/announce/2007/mfsa2007-11.html</cve>
		<desc>The FTP protocol includes the PASV (passive) command which is used by Firefox to request an alternate data port. The specification of the FTP protocol allows the server response to include an alternate server address as well, although this is rarely used in practice.
			mark@bindshell.net reported that a malicious web page hosted on a specially-coded FTP server could use this feature to perform a rudimentary port-scan of machines inside the firewall of the victim. By itself this causes no harm, but information about an internal network may be useful to an attacker should there be other vulnerabilities present on the network.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>136</id>
		<date>2007-03-24</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libwpd</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.9-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1842</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-0002
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1466</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in libwpd, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to compromise an application using the library.
			1) An integer overflow within the "WP6GeneralTextPacket::_readContents" function can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted WordPerfect document in an application using the library.
			2) Boundary errors within the "WP3TablesGroup::_readContents()" and "WP5DefinitionGroup_DefineTablesSubGroup::WP5DefinitionGroup_DefineTablesSubGroup()" functions can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows by e.g. tricking a user into opening a specially crafted WordPerfect document in an application using the library.
			Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>135</id>
		<date>2007-03-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mplayer</package>
		<vulnerable>mplayer-1.0rc1-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>mplayer-1.0rc1-4terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1838</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1246
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1387</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in MPlayer, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to boundary errors in the "DMO_VideoDecoder_Open()" function in loader/dmo/DMO_VideoDecoder.c and in the "DS_VideoDecoder_Open()" function in loader/dshow/DS_VideoDecoder.c. These can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows and may allow execution of arbitrary code via a specially crafted media file.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
