<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author?, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- If you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - read /hooks/README! -->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>704</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mantis</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.3-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.4-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4389</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4348
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4349
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4350</cve>
		<desc>Gjoko Krstic has reported some vulnerabilities in MantisBT, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and disclose sensitive information.
			1) Input passed via the "db_type" parameter to admin/upgrade_unattended.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			2) Input passed via the "db_type" parameter to admin/upgrade_unattended.php is not properly verified before being used to include files. This can be exploited to include arbitrary file from local resources via directory traversal sequences and URL-encoded NULL bytes.
			NOTE: Successful exploitation requires that installation best-practices have not been followed and the "admin" directory has not been deleted after a successful installation.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>703</id>
		<date>2011-02-06</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.2-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.3-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4387</bts>
		<cve>No CVE references, see http://wordpress.org/news/2010/12/wordpress-3-0-3/</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The security issue is caused due to the XML-RPC remote publishing interface not properly enforcing access control restrictions for editing, publishing, or deleting posts.
			Successful exploitation of this security issue requires "Author level" or "Contributor level" permissions and that remote publishing is enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>702</id>
		<date>2010-12-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.2-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4382</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4257</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct SQL injection attacks.
			Input passed via the "Send Trackbacks" field when creating a new post is not properly sanitised in wp-includes/comment.php before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires "Author-level" permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>701</id>
		<date>2010-12-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.35-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.35-2haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4384</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3848
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3849
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3850</cve>
		<desc>This fixes multiple vulnerabilities, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions, cause a DoS (Denial of Service), and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>700</id>
		<date>2010-12-12</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.35-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.35-2haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4304</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2240
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2803
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2963
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3904</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in the Linux kernel:
			1) The do_anonymous_page function in mm/memory.c does not properly separate the stack and the heap, which allows context-dependent attackers to execute arbitrary code by writing to the bottom page of a shared memory segment, as demonstrated by a memory-exhaustion attack against the X.Org X server.
			2) The drm_ioctl function in drivers/gpu/drm/drm_drv.c in the Direct Rendering Manager (DRM) subsystem allows local users to obtain potentially sensitive information from kernel memory by requesting a large memory-allocation amount.
			3) drivers/media/video/v4l2-compat-ioctl32.c in the Video4Linux (V4L) implementation on 64-bit platforms does not validate the destination of a memory copy operation, which allows local users to write to arbitrary kernel memory locations, and consequently gain privileges, via a VIDIOCSTUNER ioctl call on a /dev/video device, followed by a VIDIOCSMICROCODE ioctl call on this device.
			4) The rds_page_copy_user function in net/rds/page.c in the Reliable Datagram Sockets (RDS) protocol implementation  does not properly validate addresses obtained from user space, which allows local users to gain privileges via crafted use of the sendmsg and recvmsg system calls.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>699</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>3.3.7-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.3.8.1-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4381</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4329</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Phpmyadmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to perform an XSS attack. See http://www.phpmyadmin.net/home_page/security/PMASA-2010-8.php for details.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>698</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.1-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.2-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4380</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4300
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-4301</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) A boundary error in "dissect_ldss_transfer()" in epan/dissectors/packet-ldss.c can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
			2) An error in the ZigBee ZCL Discover Attribute Response dissector can be exploited to cause an infinite loop.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>697</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.1-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.2-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4380</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=2010-3445</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an infinite recursion error in the "dissect_unknown_ber()" function in epan/dissectors/packet-ber.c and can be exploited to cause a stack overflow e.g. via a specially crafted SNMP packet.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>696</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6-lightbox2</package>
		<vulnerable>6.x_1.9-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.x_1.10-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4326</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/919610.</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in Lightbox2 module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions and conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) A vulnerability exists in the access control mechanism for video content and can be exploited to get access to restricted video content.
			2) Input passed via unspecified parameters is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>695</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mantis</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.3-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4318</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3070
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3303
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3763</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in MantisBT, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks and by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) The application bundles a vulnerable version of NuSOAP.
			2) Certain Input passed via custom field types is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires "Manage Custom Fields" permissions.
			3) Certain input passed via project and category names is not properly sanitised before being displayed to the user in print_all_bug_page_word.php. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires "Project Manager" permissions.
			4) Input passed via the Summary field when creating an issue is not properly sanitised before being used in core/summary_api.php. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.
			Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires "Reporter" permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>694</id>
		<date>2010-11-30</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>3.3.7-1haven1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.3.8.1-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4381</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3263</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Certain unspecified input passed to the setup script is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			NOTE: Successful exploitation requires that installation best-practices have not been followed and the setup scripts have not been deleted after a successful installation.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>693</id>
		<date>2010-08-29</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>openoffice.org</package>
		<vulnerable>3.2.1-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.2.1-5haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4296</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2935
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-2936</cve>
		<desc>Charlie Miller has discovered two vulnerabilities in OpenOffice.org Impress, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
		1) An integer truncation error when parsing certain content can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted file.
		2) A short integer overflow error when parsing certain content can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted file.
		Successful exploitation of the vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>692</id>
		<date>2010-08-29</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>3.3.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.3.5.1-1haven1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4294</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-3056</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) Input passed via the "field_str" parameter to db_search.php , the "delimiter" parameter to db_sql.php, the "sort" parameter to db_structure.php, the "db" parameter to js/messages.php, the "sort_by" parameter to server_databases.php, the "checkprivs", "dbname", "pred_tablename", "selected_usr[]", "tablename", and "username" parameters to server_privileges.php, the "DefaultLang" parameter to setup/config.php, the "cpurge", "goto", "purge", "purgekey", "table", and "zero_rows" parameters to sql.php, and the "fields[multi_edit][]" parameter to tbl_replace.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			2) Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
