<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author?, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- If you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - read /hooks/README! -->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>743</id>
		<date>2011-09-09</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mantis</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.7-1mores1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.8-1mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4586</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see https://www.htbridge.ch/advisory/multiple_vulnerabilities_in_mantisbt.html</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in MantisBT, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and disclose potentially sensitive information and by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.

1) Certain input passed via the URL is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.

2) Input passed to the "action" parameter in bug_actiongroup_ext_page.php and bug_actiongroup_page.php is not properly verified before being used to include files. This can be exploited to include arbitrary files from local resources via directory traversal attacks and URL-encoded NULL bytes.

Note: In combination with MantisBT's file upload functionality, this can be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code.

3) Input passed to the "os", "os_build", and "platform" parameters in bug_report_page.php and bug_update_advanced_page.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a users browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>742</id>
		<date>2011-09-07</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>apache</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.19-2mores1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.2.20-1mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4571</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-3192</cve>
		<desc>Kingcope has discovered a vulnerability in Apache HTTP Server, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the ByteRange filter when processing requests containing a large amount of ranges, which can be exploited to exhaust memory via specially crafted HTTP requests sent to the server.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>741</id>
		<date>2011-09-03</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>foomatic-filters</package>
		<vulnerable>4.0.1-5</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.0.1-6mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4556</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2924</cve>
		<desc>It was found that foomatic-rip filter used insecurely created temporary file
for storage of PostScript data by rendering the data, intended to be sent to
the PostScript filter, when the debug mode was enabled. A local attacker could
use this flaw to conduct symlink attacks (overwrite arbitrary file accessible
with the privileges of the user running the foomatic-rip universal print
filter).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>740</id>
		<date>2011-08-29</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>3.4.3.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.4.4-1mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4567</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-3181</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Certain input passed to table, column, and index names is not properly sanitised before being used in the Tracking feature. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is being viewed.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>739</id>
		<date>2011-08-28</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>stunnel</package>
		<vulnerable>4.39-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.42-1mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4552</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2940</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Stunnel, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an unspecified error and can be exploited to corrupt heap memory.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>738</id>
		<date>2011-08-27</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>krb5</package>
		<vulnerable>1.7-6</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.7.2-1mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4256</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-0628
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1320
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-1321</cve>
		<desc>1) A vulnerability has been reported in Kerberos, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an assertion error within the "spnego_gss_accept_sec_context()" function in src/lib/gssapi/spnego/spnego_mech.c when receiving an invalid packet, which can be exploited to e.g. crash an application using the library by sending a specially crafted packet.
			2) Joel Johnson has reported a vulnerability in Kerberos, which can be exploited by malicious users to potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in KDC within the "process_tgs_req()" function in kdc/do_tgs_req.c when validating or renewing tickets and can be exploited to trigger a double-free condition.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			3) A vulnerability has been reported in Kerberos, which can be exploited by malicious users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to a NULL pointer dereference error when processing certain Kerberos AP-REQ authenticators, which can be exploited to cause a crash in e.g. kadmind or other applications linked against the GSS-API library by sending an AP-REQ authenticator with a missing checksum field.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>737</id>
		<date>2011-08-24</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mantis</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.7-1mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4553</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2938</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in MantisBT, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Input passed via the "project_id" parameter to search.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>736</id>
		<date>2011-08-23</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>roundcube</package>
		<vulnerable>0.3-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.5.4-1mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4554</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2937</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in RoundCube Webmail, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
Input passed via the "_mbox" parameter to various scripts is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>735</id>
		<date>2011-08-22</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>xpdf</package>
		<vulnerable>3.02-6</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.02-7mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4236</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-1188
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3603
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3604
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3606
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3608
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2009-3609</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Xpdf, which can be exploited by malicious people to potentially compromise a user's system.
1) Multiple integer overflows in "SplashBitmap::SplashBitmap()" can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows.
2) An integer overflow error in "ObjectStream::ObjectStream()" can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow.
3) Multiple integer overflows in "Splash::drawImage()" can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows.
4) An integer overflow error in "PSOutputDev::doImageL1Sep()" can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow when converting a PDF document to a PS file.
Successful exploitation of the vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code by tricking a user into opening a specially crafted PDF file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>734</id>
		<date>2011-08-17</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>flashplugin</package>
		<vulnerable>10.3.181.34-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>10.3.183.5-1mores1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/4545</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2130
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2134
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2135
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2136
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2137
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2138
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2139
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2140
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2414
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2415
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2416
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2417
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2424
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2011-2425</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in Adobe Flash Player, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information and compromise a user's system.
1) An unspecified error can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow and potentially execute arbitrary code.
2) An unspecified error can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow and potentially execute arbitrary code.
3) An error exists within a certain ActionScript function in the "flash.display" class when parsing certain parameters and can be exploited to corrupt memory and potentially execute arbitrary code.
4) An integer overflow error within a certain ActionScript function can be exploited to corrupt memory and potentially execute arbitrary code.
5) An unspecified error can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow and potentially execute arbitrary code.
6) An integer overflow error when handling the "scroll" method of the ActionScript Bitmap class can be exploited to corrupt memory.
7) An unspecified error can be exploited to disclose certain information from another domain.
8) An unspecified error can be exploited to corrupt memory and potentially execute arbitrary code.
9) An unspecified error can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow and potentially execute arbitrary code.
10) An error within the "Setslot()" method when parsing a certain field from an SWF file can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow and potentially execute arbitrary code.
11) An integer overflow error within a certain ActionScript function can be exploited to corrupt memory and potentially execute arbitrary code.
12) An unspecified error can be exploited to corrupt memory and potentially execute arbitrary code.
13) An error within the "Bitmapdata" class when parsing a certain field from an SWF file can be exploited to corrupt memory and potentially execute arbitrary code.
14) 80 unspecified errors of various types when parsing SWF file content may be exploited to corrupt memory.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
