<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author?, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- If you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - read /hooks/README! -->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>543</id>
		<date>2008-10-22</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.3-1solaria1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.4-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3417</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://www.wireshark.org/security/wnpa-sec-2008-06.html</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities and a weakness have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
		1) An error within the Bluetooth ACL dissector can be exploited to cause a crash via specially crafted packets.
		2) An error within the Q.931 dissector can be exploited to cause a crash via specially crafted packets.
		3) Uninitialised data structures within the Bluetooth RFCOMM and USB dissector can be exploited to cause a crash via specially crafted packets.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>542</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mantis</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.4-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3411</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://milw0rm.com/exploits/6768</cve>
		<desc>EgiX has discovered a vulnerability in Mantis, which can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
		Input passed to the "sort" parameter in manage_proj_page.php is not properly sanitised before being used in a "create_function()" call. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code.
		Successful exploitation requires valid user credentials.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>541</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>dovecot</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.4-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3387</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-4577
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-4578</cve>
		<desc>Two security issues have been reported in Dovecot, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) The problem is that the ACL plugin interprets negative access rights as positive access rights, potentially giving an unprivileged user access to restricted resources.
			2) An error in the ACL plugin when imposing mailbox creation restrictions can be exploited to create "parent/child/child" mailboxes.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>540</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mplayer</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0rc2-6</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0rc2-7solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3371</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-3827</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in MPlayer, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
		The vulnerabilities are caused due to multiple boundary errors within the "demux_real_fill_buffer()" function in libmpdemux/demux_real.c. These can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows via specially crafted Real Media files.
		Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>539</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>mediawiki</package>
		<vulnerable>1.12.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.13.2-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3382</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-4408</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in MediaWiki, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
		Input passed to the "useskin" parameter is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
		Successful exploitation requires that $wgUseSiteCss is enabled, which is the default.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>538</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>django</package>
		<vulnerable>0.96.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3372</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-3909</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Django, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site request forgery attacks.
		The vulnerability is caused due to the Django administration application not performing any validity checks to verify requests when re-authenticating the user. This can be exploited to delete and edit data when a not logged-in user e.g. visits a malicious web site and is then enticed to log in to the application.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>537</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>libpng</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.29-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.32-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3367</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-3964</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in libpng, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
		The vulnerability is caused due to an off-by-one error within the "png_push_read_zTXt()" function in pngread.c when processing malicious PNG images with specially crafted zTXt chunks, which can be exploited to crash an application using the library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>536</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>jasper</package>
		<vulnerable>1.900.1-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.900.1-3solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3396</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-3520</cve>
		<desc>Multiple integer overflows in JasPer might allow context-dependent attackers to have an unknown impact via a crafted image file, related to integer multiplication for memory allocation.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>535</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>lighttpd</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.19-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.20-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3375</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-4298
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-4359
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-4360</cve>
		<desc>A weakness and two vulnerabilities have been reported in lighttpd, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose potentially sensitive information, bypass certain security restrictions, and cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
		1) A vulnerability is caused due to a memory leak within the "http_request_parse()" function when processing duplicate request headers and can be exploited to exhaust all available memory.
		2) A vulnerability is caused due to the "mod_userdir" module not correctly handling filenames on case insensitive file systems. This can be exploited to e.g. disclose potentially sensitive information by sending requests with mixed upper and lowercase characters.
		3) A weakness is caused due to lighttpd not decoding requests before matching them with rewrite and redirect rules. This can be exploited to e.g. bypass the rewrite and redirect rules.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>534</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal-cck</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_1.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_1.9-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3347</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/304093</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in the Drupal Content Construction Kit (CCK), which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Input passed to some fields settings forms (e.g. "field label", "help text", "allowed values") is not properly sanitised before being used. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is viewed.
			Successful exploitation requires "administer content" privileges.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>533</id>
		<date>2008-10-19</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.2-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3346</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-4106
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-4107</cve>
		<desc>Stefan Esser has reported a vulnerability in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious people to guess automatically generated passwords.
		The vulnerability is caused due to WordPress using a weak pseudo random number generator to generate passwords while leaking it's state information to an attacker. In combination with other attacks this can e.g. be exploited to recover the administrator's automatically generated password.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>532</id>
		<date>2008-10-10</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal6</package>
		<vulnerable>6.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>6.5-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3393</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/318706</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions.
The vulnerability is caused due to improper access restriction in the core upload module. This can be exploited to attach arbitrary files to content, without valid credentials.
Successful exploitation requires that the core upload module is enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>531</id>
		<date>2008-10-10</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal</package>
		<vulnerable>5.10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.11-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3392</bts>
		<cve>No CVE, see http://drupal.org/node/318706</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people and users to bypass certain security restrictions.
		1) A vulnerability is caused due to improper access restriction in the core upload module. This can be exploited to retrieve files attached to content, without valid credentials for accessing the content itself.
		Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires valid user credentials and that the core upload module is enabled.
		2) A vulnerability is caused due to improper access restriction in the node module API. This can be exploited to bypass node validation under some unspecified circumstances. No further information is currently available.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>530</id>
		<date>2008-10-08</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>wireshark </package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.2-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.3-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3345</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-3146
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-3932
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-3933</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) Various errors within epan/dissectors/packet-ncp2222.inc can be exploited to cause e.g. a crash or an infinite loop via specially crafted NCP packets.
			2) An error while uncompressing zlib-compressed packet data can be exploited to cause a crash via specially crafted packets.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>529</id>
		<date>2008-09-26</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>drupal-simplenews</package>
		<vulnerable>5.x_1.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.x_1.5-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3362</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue yet, see http://drupal.org/node/312944.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Simplenews module for Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Input passed as Newsletter categories is not properly sanitised before being stored. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which is executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is viewed.
			Successful exploitation requires valid user credentials with the "administer taxonomy" permission.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>528</id>
		<date>2008-09-26</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.11.9.1-1solaria1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.11.9.2-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3361</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue yet, see http://www.phpmyadmin.net/home_page/security.php?issue=PMASA-2008-8.</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			An error exists in the "PMA_escapeJsString()" function in libraries/js_escape.lib.php, which can be exploited to bypass certain filters and execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when e.g. Microsoft Internet Explorer is used.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>527</id>
		<date>2008-09-24</date>
		<author>Miklos Vajna</author>
		<package>bitlbee</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.3-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3344</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-3969</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in BitlBee, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions and hijack accounts.
		The security issue is caused due to an unspecified error, which can be exploited to overwrite existing accounts.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>526</id>
		<date>2008-09-21</date>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.11.8.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.11.9.1-1solaria1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/3352</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2008-4096</cve>
		<desc>Norman Hippert has reported a vulnerability in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious users to compromise a vulnerable system.
			Input passed to the "sort_by" parameter in server_databases.php is not properly sanitised before being used. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary PHP code.
			Successful exploitation requires valid user credentials.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
