<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- if you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - xmllint is your friend
-->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>41</id>
		<date>2006-11-13</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.17-6siwenna1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.17-6siwenna2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1423</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5619</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the handling of seqfiles for "/proc/net/ip6_flowlabel", which can be exploited to cause kernel lockups and crashes via specially crafted flow labels.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>40</id>
		<date>2006-11-09</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>bind</package>
		<vulnerable>9.3.2_P1-1siwenna1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.3.2_P2-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1420</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-2937
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-2940</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in BIND, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions or cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to the potential use of vulnerable OpenSSL libraries.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>39</id>
		<date>2006-11-06</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>php</package>
		<vulnerable>5.1.6-2siwenna1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.1.6-3siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1419</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5465</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in PHP, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to boundary errors within the "htmlentities()" and "htmlspecialchars()" functions. If a PHP application uses these functions to process user-supplied input, this can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by passing specially crafted data to the affected application.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code, but requires that the UTF-8 character set is selected.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>38</id>
		<date>2006-11-06</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libx11</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.3-2siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1416</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5397</cve>
		<desc>Kees Cook has reported a vulnerability in libX11, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose potentially sensitive information.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a file descriptor leak in the Xinput module, which can be exploited to disclose the content of certain files.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>37</id>
		<date>2006-11-06</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mutt-devel</package>
		<vulnerable>1.5.12-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.5.12-2siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1399</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5297
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5298</cve>
		<desc>Some weaknesses have been reported in mutt, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to perform certain actions with escalated privileges.
			1) The "safe_open()" function insecurely creates temporary files on NFS directories, because the O_EXEC flag is not always correctly honored. This may be exploited to overwrite arbitrary files.
			2) A race condition exists within the "mutt_adv_mktemp()" function between calling "mktemp()" and "safe_fopen()". This may be exploited to create files with weak permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>36</id>
		<date>2006-11-06</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mutt</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.2.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.2.2-2siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1399</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5297
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5298</cve>
		<desc>Some weaknesses have been reported in mutt, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to perform certain actions with escalated privileges.
			1) The "safe_open()" function insecurely creates temporary files on NFS directories, because the O_EXEC flag is not always correctly honored. This may be exploited to overwrite arbitrary files.
			2) A race condition exists within the "mutt_adv_mktemp()" function between calling "mktemp()" and "safe_fopen()". This may be exploited to create files with weak permissions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>35</id>
		<date>2006-11-05</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>0.99.3a-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.99.4-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1376</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5468
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5740
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4805
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5469
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4574
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5595</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			Errors within the HTTP, LDAP, XOT, WBXML, and MIME parsers can be exploited to cause a crash or consume large amounts of memory when parsing a specially crafted packet that is either captured off the wire or loaded via a capture file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>34</id>
		<date>2006-10-31</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wv</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.4-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1374</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4513</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in wvWare, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to integer overflows within the "wvGetLFO_records()" and "wvGetLFO_PLF()" functions. These can be exploited to cause heap-based buffer overflows by e.g. tricking a user to open a specially crafted Microsoft Word document with an application using the library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>33</id>
		<date>2006-10-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>postgresql</package>
		<vulnerable>8.1.4-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>8.1.5-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1367</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue, see: http://secunia.com/advisories/22562</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in PostgreSQL, which can be exploited by malicious users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) An incorrect type check before coercing unknown literals into the ANYARRAY type can be exploited to cause a crash when converting certain literals into ANYARRAY.
			2) An error exists within the handling of aggregate functions in UPDATE statements, which can be exploited to crash the server backend.
			3) An error within the logging of V3-protocol execute messages of ROLLBACK or COMMIT statements can be exploited to cause a crash.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>32</id>
		<date>2006-10-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>screen</package>
		<vulnerable>4.0.2-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.0.3-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1366</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4573</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in GNU Screen, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to errors within the handling of certain UTF-8 characters. This can be exploited to crash GNU Screen or potentially execute arbitrary code by printing a specially crafted string to the window.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>31</id>
		<date>2006-10-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>cscope</package>
		<vulnerable>15.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>15.6-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1340</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4262</cve>
		<desc>Will Drewry has reported some vulnerabilities in Cscope, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) Various boundary errors within the parsing of file lists or the expansion of environment variables can be exploited to cause stack-based buffer overflows when parsing specially crafted "cscope.lists" files or directories.
			2) A boundary error within the parsing of command line arguments can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow when supplying an overly long "reffile" argument.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>30</id>
		<date>2006-10-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>drupal</package>
		<vulnerable>4.7.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.7.3-2siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1338</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue, see: http://secunia.com/advisories/22486</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks, and by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting and cross-site request forgery attacks.
			1) Some unspecified input is not properly sanitised in the XML parser before being used. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site via a specially crafted RSS feed. Successful exploitation requires that the PHP "mbstring" extension is disabled.
			2) Some unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being used in the "aggregator", "profile", and "forum" module. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			3) An error exists due to the application allowing users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any validity checks to verify the user's request. This can e.g. be exploited to change passwords, post PHP code, or create new users.
			4) Some input to unspecified parameters is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to redirect a user's form submission to an attackers site when the user is tricked to use a specially crafted link.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>29</id>
		<date>2006-10-24</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>asterisk</package>
		<vulnerable>asterisk-1.2.11-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>asterisk-1.2.13-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1339</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE entry for this issue, see: http://lists.grok.org.uk/pipermail/full-disclosure/2006-October/050171.html</cve>
		<desc>Adam Boileau has reported a vulnerability in Asterisk, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow within the "get_input()" function in chan_skinny.c. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by sending specially crafted packets to the Asterisk Skinny channel driver.
			Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code, but requires that "chan_skinny" is loaded.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>28</id>
		<date>2006-10-24</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>nvidia</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0_8774-4siwenna1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0_8776-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1326</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE entry for this issue, see: http://www.rapid7.com/advisories/R7-0025.jsp</cve>
		<desc>Rapid7 has reported a vulnerability in NVIDIA Binary Graphics Driver for Linux, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges and potentially by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			A boundary error when performing accelerated rendering of glyphs can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow via a specially crafted short sequence of user-supplied glyphs.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code with "root" privileges.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>27</id>
		<date>2006-10-24</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>qt4</package>
		<vulnerable>4.1.4-5</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.1.4-6</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1336</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4811</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Qt, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow within the way Qt handles certain pixmap images. This can potentially be exploited to execute arbitrary code by e.g. causing an application linked against Qt to process a specially crafted pixmap image.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>26</id>
		<date>2006-10-24</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>qt</package>
		<vulnerable>3.3.6-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.3.6-5</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1335</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4811</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Qt, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow within the way Qt handles certain pixmap images. This can potentially be exploited to execute arbitrary code by e.g. causing an application linked against Qt to process a specially crafted pixmap image.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>25</id>
		<date>2006-10-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.17-5</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.17-6siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1323</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4623</cve>
		<desc>Ang Way Chuang has reported a vulnerability in Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
		The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the ULE (Unidirectional Lightweight Encapsulation) decapsulation code when processing ULE packets. This can be exploited to crash the system by sending a malicious ULE packet with an SNDU (Sub Network Data Unit) size of 0</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>24</id>
		<date>2006-10-19</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>clamav</package>
		<vulnerable>0.88.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.88.5-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1316</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4182
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5295</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in Clam AntiVirus, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>23</id>
		<date>2006-10-12</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>python</package>
		<vulnerable>2.4.3-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.4.3-4siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1284</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4980</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Python, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>22</id>
		<date>2006-10-11</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>php</package>
		<vulnerable>5.1.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.1.6-2siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1266
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1291</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4625
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4812</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in PHP, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
		Maksymilian Arciemowicz has reported a vulnerability in PHP, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>21</id>
		<date>2006-10-10</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mono</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.17.1-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.17.2-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1261</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5072</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Mono, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to perform certain actions with escalated privileges.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>20</id>
		<date>2006-10-09</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>j2sdk</package>
		<vulnerable>5.0_08-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.0_09-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1251</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4339</cve>
		<desc>Sun has acknowledged a vulnerability in Sun JDK / SDK, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>19</id>
		<date>2006-10-09</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>j2re</package>
		<vulnerable>5.0_08-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.0_09-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1251</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4339</cve>
		<desc>Sun has acknowledged a vulnerability in Sun JDK / SDK, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>18</id>
		<date>2006-10-03</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openvpn</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.8-1siwenna1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.9-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1246</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-2937
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-2940
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-3738
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4343</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in OpenVPN, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>17</id>
		<date>2006-10-03</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>gst-ffmpeg</package>
		<vulnerable>0.10.1-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.10.1-3siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1239</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4800</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in GStreamer FFmpeg Plug-in, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>16</id>
		<date>2006-10-03</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>gzip-devel</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.5-2siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/1210</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4334
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4335
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4336
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4337
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4338</cve>
		<desc>Tavis Ormandy has reported some vulnerabilities in gzip, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>15</id>
		<date>2006-10-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.8.2.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.9.1_rc1-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1229</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE entry for this issue, see: http://secunia.com/advisories/22126</cve>
		<desc>Sebastian Mendel, Stefan Esser, and Michael Heimpold Some have reported Some vulnerabilities with unknown impacts in phpMyAdmin.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>14</id>
		<date>2006-10-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openvpn</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.8-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1162</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4339</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in OpenVPN, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>13</id>
		<date>2006-10-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>bind</package>
		<vulnerable>9.3.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.3.2_P1-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1161</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4095
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4096</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in BIND, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>12</id>
		<date>2006-10-01</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openssh</package>
		<vulnerable>4.3p2-4siwenna1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.4p1-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1235</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5051
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-5052</cve>
		<desc>Mark Dowd reported a vulnerability in OpenSSH, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise of a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>11</id>
		<date>2006-10-01</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openssl</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.8-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.8-5siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1228</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-2937
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-2940
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-3738
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4343</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in OpenSSL, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and compromise a vulnerable system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>10</id>
		<date>2006-09-30</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mailman</package>
		<vulnerable>2.1.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.1.9-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1101</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-2191
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-2941
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-3636
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4624</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mailman, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting and phishing attacks, and cause a DoS (Denial of Service).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>9</id>
		<date>2006-09-30</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openssh</package>
		<vulnerable>4.3p2-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.3p2-4siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1215</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4924</cve>
		<desc>Tavis Ormandy has reported a vulnerability in OpenSSH, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>8</id>
		<date>2006-09-30</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>flashplugin</package>
		<vulnerable>7.0r63-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>7.0r68-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1160</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-3014
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-3311
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4640</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in Adobe Flash Player, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions or compromise a user's system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>7</id>
		<date>2006-09-30</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>seamonkey</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.5-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1146</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4253
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4340
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4565
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4566
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4568
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4570
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4571</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mozilla SeaMonkey, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct spoofing attacks, bypass certain security restrictions, and potentially compromise a user's system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>6</id>
		<date>2006-09-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>thunderbird</package>
		<vulnerable>1.5.0.5-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.5.0.7-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1145</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4253
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4340
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4565
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4566
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4567
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4570
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4571</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mozilla Thunderbird, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct man-in-the-middle attacks, bypass certain security restrictions, and potentially compromise a user's system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>5</id>
		<date>2006-09-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>gnutls</package>
		<vulnerable>1.5.0-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.5.1-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1196</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4790</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in GnuTLS, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions. The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the verification of certain signatures.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>4</id>
		<date>2006-09-26</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>1.5.0.6-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.5.0.7-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1147</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4253
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4340
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4565
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4566
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4567
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4568
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4571</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct man-in-the-middle, spoofing, and cross-site scripting attacks, and potentially compromise a user's system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>3</id>
		<date>2006-09-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>gzip</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.4b-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.4b-2siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1189</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4334
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4335
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4336
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4337
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4338</cve>
		<desc>Tavis Ormandy from the Google Security Team discovered several vulnerabilities in gzip, the GNU compression utility.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>2</id>
		<date>2006-09-18</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>nss</package>
		<vulnerable>3.11.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.11.3-2siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1148</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-4340</cve>
		<desc>nss is Mozilla's Network Security Services library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>1</id>
		<date>2006-09-16</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libxfont</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.0-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.2-1siwenna1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/1137</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-3739,
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2006-3740</cve>
		<desc>libxfont is the X.Org Xfont library</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
