<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE fsas [
<!ELEMENT fsas (fsa)*>
<!ELEMENT fsa (id , date , author, package, vulnerable , unaffected , bts , cve , desc)>
<!-- must be an integer -->
<!ELEMENT id (#PCDATA)>
<!-- in YYYY-MM-DD format -->
<!ELEMENT date (#PCDATA)>
<!-- your nick, then the From header will be something like "nick <noreply@frugalware.org>" -->
<!ELEMENT author (#PCDATA)>
<!-- package name, without group, version, etc -->
<!ELEMENT package (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the old version -->
<!ELEMENT vulnerable (#PCDATA)>
<!-- the new (backported) version -->
<!ELEMENT unaffected (#PCDATA)>
<!-- bts url -->
<!ELEMENT bts (#PCDATA)>
<!-- cve url -->
<!ELEMENT cve (#PCDATA)>
<!-- description, can be more than one line -->
<!ELEMENT desc (#PCDATA)>
]>

<!-- if you modify this file, be sure it's still valid - xmllint is your friend
-->

<fsas>
	<fsa>
		<id>365</id>
		<date>2008-01-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>joomla</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.13-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.13-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2487</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5427</cve>
		<desc>MustLive has discovered a vulnerability in Joomla!, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Input passed to the "searchword" parameter in index.php (when "option" is set to "com_search") is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			Successful exploitation requires that the victim changes the number of search results in a drop-down box, after having clicked on the malicious link.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>364</id>
		<date>2008-01-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>postgresql</package>
		<vulnerable>8.2.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>8.2.6-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2714</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4769
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4772
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6600
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6601
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6067</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in PostgreSQL, which can be exploited by malicious users to gain escalated privileges or to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) Index functions are executed as superuser during "VACUUM" and "ANALYZE", which can be exploited to gain escalated privileges.
			2) "SET ROLE" and "SET SESSION AUTHORIZATION" are permitted within index functions, which can be exploited to gain escalated privileges.
			3) Various errors in the processing of regular expressions within SQL queries can be exploited to cause infinite loops, consume large amounts of memory, or to crash the backend, resulting in a DoS.
			4) Errors in the DBLink module can be exploited to gain superuser privileges when being used in combination with local trust or ident authentication.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>363</id>
		<date>2008-01-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libcdio</package>
		<vulnerable>0.78.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.78.2-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2713</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6613</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in the cd-info and iso-info applications of libcdio, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to boundary errors within the function "print_iso9660_recurse()" in cd-info.c and iso-info.c. This be exploited to cause a buffer overflow by e.g. tricking a user into using the iso-info application on a specially crafted ISO image.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>362</id>
		<date>2008-01-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>rsync</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.9-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.9-3sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2653</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6199
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6200</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in rsync, which can be exploited by malicious users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) An error in the rsync daemon when the "use chroot" option is disabled can be exploited to gain access to files outside of the module's hierarchy via symlink attacks.
			2) An error exists within the enforcing of the "exclude", "exclude from", and "filter" options. This can be exploited to bypass access restrictions and gain access to hidden files via e.g. symlink attacks, if the filename is known.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>361</id>
		<date>2008-01-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>asterisk</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.13-1sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.13-1sayshell2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2652</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6171
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6170
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6430</cve>
		<desc>Multiple vulnerabilities has been reported in Asterisk, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct SQL injection attacks, bypass certain security restrictions and cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) Input passed as lookup data to the Postgres Realtime Engine is not properly sanitised before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code. Successful exploitation requires that the module is configured and used.
			2) Input passed as ANI and DNIS strings to the Call Detail Record Postgres logging engine is not properly sanitised before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code. Successful exploitation requires valid user credentials and that the module is configured and used.
			3) The security issue is caused due to missing checks of IP addresses when processing database-based registrations ("realtime"). This can be exploited to authenticate as a legitimate user without a password. Successful exploitation requires that host-based authentication is used and that the attacker has knowledge of a valid username.
			4) The vulnerability is caused due to a null-pointer dereference error within the handling of the "BYE/Also" transfer method and can be exploited to crash the application. Successful exploitation requires that a dialog has already been established.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>360</id>
		<date>2008-01-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>ruby-gnome2</package>
		<vulnerable>0.16.0-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.16.0-4sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2650</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6183</cve>
		<desc>Chris Rohlf has reported a vulnerability in Ruby-GNOME2, which can potentially be exploited by malicious people to compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a format string error within the "Gtk::MessageDialog.new()" method in gtk/src/rbgtkmessagedialog.c and can potentially be exploited to execute arbitrary code when a specially crafted string is passed to the affected function.
			NOTE: Exploitation and impact of this vulnerability depend on how an application uses the affected function of the vulnerable library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>359</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libxml2</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.30-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.30-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2700</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6284</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Libxml2, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an unspecified error within the "xmlCurrentChar()" function. This can be exploited to trigger the execution of an infinite loop via specially crafted UTF-8 sequences.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>358</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>horde-webmail</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.1-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.1-4sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2693</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6018</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered a vulnerability in IMP Webmail Client and Horde Groupware Webmail Edition, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions and manipulate data.
			The HTML filter does not filter out frame and frameset HTML elements. Additionally, the application allows users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any validity checks to verify the request. This can be exploited to (a) delete an arbitrary number of e-mail messages by referencing their numeric IDs and (b) purge deleted mails, when the victim opens a malicious HTML mail.
					Successful exploitation requires that the victim opens the HTML part of a malicious message.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>357</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>drupal</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2-2sayshell2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2-2sayshell3</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2692</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE entry for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting, script insertion, and cross-site request forgery attacks.
			1) Input passed via unspecified parameters to theme .tpl.php files is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site. Successful exploitation requires that "register_globals" is enabled, and the .htaccess file fails to prevent access to .tpl.php files and to disable "register_globals".
			2) An error in the text filtering functionality can be exploited to bypass the filter via invalid UTF-8 sequences. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which will be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is viewed with e.g. Internet Explorer 6.
			3) The aggregator module allows users to perform certain actions via HTTP GET requests without performing any validity checks to verify the request. This can be exploited to e.g. remove items from a particular feed when a user visits a specially crafted page.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>356</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mantis</package>
		<vulnerable>1.0.8-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.0.8-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2683</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6611</cve>
		<desc>seiji has discovered a vulnerability in Mantis, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion attacks.
			Input passed as the filename for the uploaded file in bug_report.php is not properly sanitised before being stored. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which is executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious filename is viewed in view.php.
			Successful exploitation requires valid user credentials.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>355</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>vlc</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.6-7</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.6-8sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2682</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE entry for these issues.</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been discovered in VLC Media Player, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) Boundary errors in the "ParseMicroDvd()", "ParseSSA()", and "ParseVplayer()" functions when handling subtitles can be exploited to cause stack-based buffer overflows.
			2) A format string error in the web interface listening on port 8080/tcp (disabled by default) can be exploited via a specially crafted HTTP request with a "Connection" header value containing format specifiers. Successful exploitation of the vulnerabilities allows execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>354</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libexif</package>
		<vulnerable>0.6.16-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.6.16-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2680</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6351
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6352</cve>
		<desc>Two vulnerabilities have been reported in libexif, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or to compromise an application using the library.
			1) An integer overflow error in the "exif_data_load_data_thumbnail()" function in exif-data.c when processing exif image tags can be exploited to cause a memory corruption and may allow execution of arbitrary code via a specially crafted exif file.
			2) An infinite recursion error in the "exif_loader_write()" function in exif-loader.c when handling exif image tags can be exploited to cause an application to crash via a specially crafted exif file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>353</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>clamav</package>
		<vulnerable>0.91.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.91.2-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2679</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6335
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6336
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6337</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in ClamAV, where one vulnerability has an unknown impact and others can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) An integer overflow error exists within the "cli_scanpe()" function when handling MEW packed executables. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via specially crafted "ssize" and "dsize" values. Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.
			2) An off-by-one error exists within libclamav/mspack.c when handling MSZIP compressed files. This can be exploited to e.g. crash the scanner or potentially execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted MSZIP compressed file.
			3) An boundary error exists within the bzip2 "BZ_GET_FAST()" and "BZ_GET_FAST_C()" decompression macros in libclamav/nsis/bzlib_private.h.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>352</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>opera</package>
		<vulnerable>9.24-1sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.25-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2677</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6520
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6521
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6522
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6524</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Opera, which can be exploited by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions, disclose sensitive information, and compromise a user's system.
			1) An unspecified error can be exploited via certain plugins to conduct cross-domain scripting attacks.
			2) An unspecified error within the processing of TLS certificates can be exploited to execute arbitrary code.
			3) An unspecified error within Rich text editing when using designMode can be exploited to conduct cross-domain scripting attacks.
			4) An unspecified error within the processing of bitmaps can be exploited to disclose the contents of random memory areas.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>351</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>cups</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.2-2sayshell2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.2-2sayshell3</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2676</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5849</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in CUPS, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a signedness error within the "asn1_get_string()" function in backend/snmp.c. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow via specially crafted SNMP responses containing ASN1 encoded strings with negative length values.
			Successful exploitation on 1.3.x versions requires that the snmp backend is configured in snmp.conf.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>350</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>syslog-ng</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.5-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.5-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2675</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6437</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in syslog-ng, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to the improper processing of incoming timestamps. This can be exploited to trigger a NULL pointer dereference via a specially crafted message containing a timestamp without a terminating space character.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>349</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>apache</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.2.6-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2671</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5000</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability have been reported in Apache mod_imagemap module, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Certain unspecified input passed to "mod_imagemap" is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			Successful exploitation requires that "mod_imagemap" is enabled and a mapfile is publicly accessible.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>348</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>scponly</package>
		<vulnerable>4.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>4.6-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2662</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6350</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in scponly, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to bypass certain security restrictions.
			The security issue is caused due to the unsafe execution of certain programs (e.g. svn, svnserve, rsync or unison) and can be exploited to execute arbitrary programs via various parameters.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>347</id>
		<date>2008-01-21</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>squid</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.STABLE16-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.STABLE16-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2659</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6239</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Squid, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the processing of cache update replies and can be exploited to crash an affected server.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>346</id>
		<date>2008-01-17</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>e2fsprogs</package>
		<vulnerable>1.40.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.40.2-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2661</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5497</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in the libext2fs library of e2fsprogs, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to integer overflows, which potentially can be exploited to execute arbitrary code by e.g. tricking a user into processing a specially crafted file system with an application using libext2fs.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>345</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>claws-mail</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.1-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2655</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6208</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in Claws Mail, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to perform certain actions with escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused due to the sylprint.pl script using temporary files in an insecure manner. This can be exploited to overwrite or delete arbitrary files via symlink attacks.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>344</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>cairo</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.10-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2654</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5503</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Cairo, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise an application using the library.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an integer overflow error within the "read_png()" function in cairo-png.c. This can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted PNG file.
			Successful exploitation may allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>343</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wesnoth</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.6-2terminus1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.8-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2648</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5742
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6201</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Wesnoth, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service), disclose potentially sensitive information, or potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) An error within the WML preprocessor can be exploited via a malicious add-on to disclose the content of arbitrary files on an affected system when processing pathnames that contain directory traversal sequences.
			2) An error within the handling of the "turn_cmd" option can be exploited to cause a DoS or potentially execute arbitrary commands via a malicious add-on.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>342</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>2.3.1-1sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.3.2-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2646</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE entry for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities and a security issue have been reported in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious users to disclose potentially sensitive information and by malicious people to bypass certain security restrictions and to disclose sensitive or system information.
			1) The application does not properly restrict access to posted drafts to users with valid administrator credentials. This can be exploited to read drafts by accessing the index.php script with data in the "PATH_INFO" URL part ending with "wp-admin/".
			2) The XMLRPC function "metaWeblog.getRecentPosts" does not correctly verify that users have edit rights for a post before disclosing the "post_password".
			3) A security issue is caused due to certain database error messages containing system information (e.g. table names).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>341</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>drupal</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2-2sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2-2sayshell2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2620</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6299</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct SQL injection attacks.
			Input passed to the "taxonomy_select_nodes()" function is not properly sanitised before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code.
			Successful exploitation requires that a module that passes unsanitised data to "taxonomy_select_nodes()" is installed.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>340</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>liferea</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.23-2sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.23-2sayshell2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2606</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in Liferea, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused due to the Liferea starter script incorrectly setting the environment variable LD_LIBRARY_PATH. This can be exploited to gain escalated privileges e.g. by tricking a user into running Liferea in a directory containing a malicious library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>339</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>cacti</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.6j-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.6j-3terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2594</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6035</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Cacti, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to conduct SQL injection attacks.
			Certain unspecified input is not properly sanitised before being used in an SQL query. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>338</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>thunderbird</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.6-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.9-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2515</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5340</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mozilla Thunderbird, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) Various errors in the browser engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption.
			2) Various errors in the Javascript engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>337</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>wireshark</package>
		<vulnerable>0.99.6-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.99.7-1terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2605</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6114
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6117
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6118
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6120
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6121
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6111
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6112
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6113
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6115
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6116
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6119
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6438
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6439
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6441
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6450
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6451</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Wireshark, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerabilities are caused due to various errors (e.g. large loops with extreme memory consumption, endless loops, crashes, and buffer overflows) within the following:
			* SSL, ANSI MAP, Firebird/Interbase, NCP, HTTP, MEGACO, DCP ETSI, PPP, Bluetooth SDP, SMB, USB, WiMAX, RPL, and CIP dissectors
			* when processing a malformed MP3 or iSeries (OS/400) Communication trace file
			* when processing a malformed DNP or RPC Portmap packet
			These can be exploited to crash Wireshark or consume large amounts of system resources by e.g. parsing a specially crafted packet that is either captured off the wire or loaded via a capture file.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>336</id>
		<date>2008-01-15</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>seamonkey</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.5-1sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.7-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2608</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5947
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5959
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5960</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mozilla SeaMonkey, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting and cross-site request forgery attacks and potentially to compromise a user's system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>335</id>
		<date>2008-01-13</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>samba</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.26-2sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.26-2sayshell2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2666</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6015</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered a vulnerability in Samba, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the "send_mailslot()" function. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow with zero bytes via a specially crafted "SAMLOGON" domain logon packet containing a username string placed at an odd offset followed by an overly long GETDC string.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code, but requires that the "domain logons" option is enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>334</id>
		<date>2008-01-12</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>mysql</package>
		<vulnerable>5.0.45-2sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.0.45-2sayshell2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2669</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5969
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6303
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-6304</cve>
		<desc>A security issue and two vulnerabilities have been reported in MySQL, which can be exploited by malicious users to gain escalated privileges, manipulate certain data, or to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
		1) A security issue exists due to the command "ALTER VIEW" retaining the original "DEFINER" value, which may allow another user to gain the access rights of the view.
		2) An error in the FEDERATED engine when handling responses of remote servers can be exploited to crash the local server when the response contains fewer columns than expected.
		3) An error when renaming a table can be exploited by malicious users to manipulate certain data.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>333</id>
		<date>2008-01-11</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>openoffice.org</package>
		<vulnerable>2.3.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.3.0-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2663</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4575</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in OpenOffice, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the improper enforcing of security restrictions when passing SQL queries to the HSQLDB database engine. This can be exploited to call arbitrary static Java methods by tricking the user into executing a specially crafted SQL query contained within a database document.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>332</id>
		<date>2008-01-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.8-1sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.11-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2572</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5947
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5959
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5960</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			The problem is that the "jar:" protocol handler does not validate the MIME type of the contents of an archive, which are then executed in the context of the site hosting the archive. This can be exploited to conduct cross-site scripting attacks on sites that allow a user to upload certain files (e.g. .zip, .png, .doc, .odt, .txt).
			Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site request forgery attacks and potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) A race condition when setting the "window.location" property can be exploited to generate a fake HTTP Referer header, which can be used to conduct cross-site request forgery attacks.
			2) Some errors within the XBL component, the "drawImage()" function, and the "nsCSSFrameConstructor" can be exploited to cause memory corruption and potentially allow execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>331</id>
		<date>2008-01-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>pidgin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.2.1-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2539</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4999</cve>
		<desc>A weakness has been reported in Pidgin, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The weakness is caused due to a NULL-pointer dereference error when processing messages with invalid HTML code and can be exploited to cause libpurple to crash. Successful exploitation may require that HTML logging is used.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>330</id>
		<date>2007-12-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>cups</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.2-2sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.2-2sayshell2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2596</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5392
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5393</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in CUPS, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially to compromise a user's system.	The vulnerabilities are caused due to the use of a vulnerable version of Xpdf.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>329</id>
		<date>2007-12-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>mysql</package>
		<vulnerable>5.0.45-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.0.45-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2577</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5925</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in MySQL, which can be exploited by malicious users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an assertion error within the InnoDB engine and can be exploited to crash the database server via certain "CONTAINS" statements.
			Successful exploitation requires "ALTER" privileges.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>328</id>
		<date>2007-12-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>php-pear-mdb2</package>
		<vulnerable>2.4.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.4.1-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2573</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5934</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in PEAR MDB2, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information.
			The security issue is caused due to MDB2 potentially making use of PHP's protocol wrappers when storing certain input as LOB. This can be exploited to e.g. disclose sensitive information by storing a specially crafted URI (e.g. "file:///etc/passwd") as LOB.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>327</id>
		<date>2007-12-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>emacs</package>
		<vulnerable>22.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>22.1-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2566</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5795</cve>
		<desc>Drake Wilson has reported a vulnerability in GNU Emacs, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the "hack-local-variables" function where local variables within a file are processed in an insecure manner. This can be exploited to e.g. modify a user's user-init-file and execute arbitrary Emacs Lisp code when a specially crafted file is opened.
			Successful exploitation requires that "enable-local-variables" is set to ":safe".</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>326</id>
		<date>2007-11-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>samba</package>
		<vulnerable>3.0.26-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.0.26-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2589</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5398
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4572</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Samba, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) A boundary error exists within the "reply_netbios_packet()" function in nmbd/nmbd_packets.c when sending NetBIOS replies. This can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow by sending multiple specially crafted WINS "Name Registration" requests followed by a WINS "Name Query" request. Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code, but requires that Samba is configured to run as a WINS server (the "wins support" option is enabled).
			2) A boundary error exists within the processing of GETDC logon requests. This can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow by sending specially crafted GETDC mailslot requests. Successful exploitation of the vulnerability requires that Samba is configured as a Primary or Backup Domain Controller.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>325</id>
		<date>2007-11-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.11.1.2-1sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.11.2.2-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2578
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2588</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5976
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5977</cve>
		<desc>Three vulnerabilities have been reported in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious users to conduct script insertion, SQL injection and cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) Input passed to the "db" parameter in db_create.php is not properly sanitised before being stored. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTML and script code, which is executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site when the malicious data is viewed. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has CREATE DATABASE credentials, that the target user has valid user credentials, and that the target user uses a web browser that executes JavaScript code in img HTML elements (e.g. Opera).
			2) Input passed to the "db" parameter in db_create.php is not properly sanitised before being used in SQL queries. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code.	Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has CREATE DATABASE credentials.
			3) Tim Brown has discovered a vulnerability in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks. Input passed to the "convcharset" parameter in index.php (when "auth_type" in the configuration is set to "cookie") is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>324</id>
		<date>2007-11-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>php</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2.5-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2576</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4887</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities and weaknesses have been reported in PHP, where some have unknown impacts and others can be exploited to bypass certain security restrictions.
			1) Various errors exist in the "htmlentities" and "htmlspecialchars" functions where partial multibyte sequences are not accepted.
			2) Various boundary errors exist in the "fnmatch()", "setlocale()", and "glob()" functions and can be exploited to cause buffer overflows.
			3) An error in the processing of the "mail.force_extra_parameters" directive within an ".htaccess" file can be exploited to bypass the "safe_mode" directive.
			4) An error in the handling of variables can be exploited to overwrite values set in httpd.conf via the "ini_set()" function.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>323</id>
		<date>2007-11-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>cpio</package>
		<vulnerable>2.9-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.9-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2570</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4476</cve>
		<desc>There is a vulnerability in cpio, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error when processing specially crafted tar archives and can be exploited to cause a stack-based buffer overflow and crash the vulnerable application.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>322</id>
		<date>2007-11-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>perl</package>
		<vulnerable>5.8.8-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.8.8-5sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2568</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5116</cve>
		<desc>Tavis Ormandy and Will Drewry have reported a vulnerability in Perl, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the processing of regular expressions containing Unicode data. This can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow via a specially crafted regular expression causing a runtime switch to the Unicode character scheme.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>321</id>
		<date>2007-11-27</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openldap</package>
		<vulnerable>2.3.38-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.3.39-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2542</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5707
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5708</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in OpenLDAP, which can be exploited by malicious users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) A vulnerability is caused due to the "add_filter_attrs()" function in servers/slapd/overlay/pcache.c not correctly NULL terminating "new_attrs", which can be exploited to crash slapd due to an out of bounds memory access. Successful exploitation may require that slapd runs as proxy-caching server.
			2) An error within the normalisation of "objectClasses" can be exploited to crash a vulnerable server by sending a malformed "objectClasses" attribute.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>320</id>
		<date>2007-11-25</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.22-7sayshell2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.22-7sayshell3</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2599</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5500
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5501</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious, local users and by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) An error within the "wait_task_stopped()" function can be exploited to cause a DoS by manipulating the state of a child process while the parent is waiting for the state to change (e.g. the parent is inside "wait()" or "waitpid()").
			2) An NULL-pointer dereference error exists within the "tcp_sacktag_write_queue()" function when processing ACK packets. This can be exploited to crash an affected system via specially crafted ACK packets.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>319</id>
		<date>2007-11-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>poppler</package>
		<vulnerable>0.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.6-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2561</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5392
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5393</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Poppler, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise an application using the library. The vulnerabilities are caused due to the use of vulnerable Xpdf code. For more information: FSA-316</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>318</id>
		<date>2007-11-17</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>kdegraphics</package>
		<vulnerable>3.5.7-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.5.7-3sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2560</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5392
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5393</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in KOffice, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system. The vulnerabilities are caused due to the use of vulnerable Xpdf code. For more information: FSA-316</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>317</id>
		<date>2007-11-17</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>koffice</package>
		<vulnerable>1.6.3-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.6.3-3sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2559</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5392
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5393</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in KOffice, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system. The vulnerabilities are caused due to the use of vulnerable Xpdf code. For more information: FSA-316</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>316</id>
		<date>2007-11-17</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>xpdf</package>
		<vulnerable>3.02-3</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>3.02-4sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2558</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4352
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5392
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5393</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered some vulnerabilities in Xpdf, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a user's system.
			1) An array indexing error within the "DCTStream::readProgressiveDataUnit()" method in xpdf/Stream.cc can be exploited to corrupt memory via a specially crafted PDF file.
			2) An integer overflow error within the "DCTStream::reset()" method in xpdf/Stream.cc can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow via a specially crafted PDF file.
			3) A boundary error within the "CCITTFaxStream::lookChar()" method in xpdf/Stream.cc can be exploited to cause a heap-based buffer overflow by tricking a user into opening a PDF file containing a specially crafted "CCITTFaxDecode" filter.
			Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>315</id>
		<date>2007-11-12</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.22-7sayshell1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.22-7sayshell2</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2562</bts>
		<cve>CVE-2007-4997</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in the Linux Kernel, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an off-by-two error within the function "ieee80211_rx()" in net/ieee80211/ieee80211_rx.c. This can be exploited to cause a kernel panic by sending a specially crafted ieee80211 frame with the IEEE80211_STYPE_QOS_DATA flag set to an affected system.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>314</id>
		<date>2007-11-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>liferea</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.23-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.23-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2544</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5751</cve>
		<desc>A security issue has been reported in Liferea, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to disclose sensitive information.
			The security issue is caused due to incorrect file permissions being set for the "feedlist.opml" backup file. This can be exploited to retrieve feed or proxy authentication usernames and passwords.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>313</id>
		<date>2007-11-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>django</package>
		<vulnerable>0.96-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.96-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2543</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5712</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Django, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to the Django internationalization system ("i18n") incorrectly processing HTTP headers. This can be exploited to allocate large amounts of memory by sending specially crafted HTTP "Accept-Language" requests.	Successful exploitation requires that the "USE_I18N" option and the "i18n" middleware component are enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>312</id>
		<date>2007-11-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>cups</package>
		<vulnerable>1.3.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.3.2-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2540</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4351</cve>
		<desc>Secunia Research has discovered a vulnerability in CUPS, which can be exploited by malicious people to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the "ippReadIO()" function in cups/ipp.c when processing IPP (Internet Printing Protocol) tags. This can be exploited to overwrite one byte on the stack with a zero by sending an IPP request containing specially crafted "textWithLanguage" or "nameWithLanguage" tags. Successful exploitation allows execution of arbitrary code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>311</id>
		<date>2007-11-02</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wordpress</package>
		<vulnerable>2.2.3-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.3.1-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2535</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5710</cve>
		<desc>Janek Vind has discovered a vulnerability in WordPress, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			Input passed to the "posts_columns" parameter in wp-admin/edit-post-rows.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site. Successful exploitation requires that "register_globals" is enabled.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>310</id>
		<date>2007-11-01</date>
		<author>vmiklos</author>
		<package>kernel</package>
		<vulnerable>2.6.22-6</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.6.22-7sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2455</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3731</cve>
		<desc>Evan Teran has reported a security issue in the Linux kernel, which potentially can be exploited by malicious, local users to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in ptrace when single-stepping a debugged child process with invalid values in the "CS" register, which can be exploited to cause a kernel oops.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>309</id>
		<date>2007-10-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>asterisk-addons</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.4-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2506</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5488</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Asterisk-Addons, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct SQL injection attacks.
			Input passed via the source and destination numbers are not properly sanitised in the "cdr_addon_mysql" module before being used in an SQL query. This can be exploited to manipulate SQL queries by injecting arbitrary SQL code.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>308</id>
		<date>2007-10-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>asterisk</package>
		<vulnerable>1.4.11-2</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.4.13-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2494</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5358</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Asterisk, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) or potentially to compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to a boundary error within the IMAP-specific code for processing voicemail messages. This can be exploited to cause a buffer overflow via a specially crafted voicemail message sent as email containing an overly long (more than 1024 characters) combination of Content-Type or Content-Description headers.
			Successful exploitation requires that a user listens to the voicemail message via a phone.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>307</id>
		<date>2007-10-25</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>tomboy</package>
		<vulnerable>0.8.0-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.8.0-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2370</bts>
		<cve>There is no CVE for this issue.</cve>
		<desc>Jab Oravec has reported a security issue in Tomboy, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			The security issue is caused due to the "/usr/bin/tomboy" script incorrectly setting the environment variable LD_LIBRARY_PATH. This can be exploited to gain escalated privileges by e.g. tricking a user into running Tomboy in a directory containing a malicious library.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>306</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>seamonkey</package>
		<vulnerable>1.1.4-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.1.5-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2514</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1095
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2292
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4841
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5334
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5337
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5338
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5340</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities and a weakness have been reported in Mozilla SeaMonkey, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information, conduct phishing attacks, manipulate certain data, and potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) Various errors in the browser engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption.
			2) Various errors in the Javascript engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			3) An error in the handling of onUnload events can be exploited to read and manipulate the document's location of new pages.
			4) Input passed to the user ID when making an HTTP request using Digest Authentication is not properly sanitised before being used in a request. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTTP headers into a user's request when a proxy is used.
			5) An error when displaying web pages written in the XUL markup language can be exploited to hide the window's title bar and facilitate phishing attacks.
			6) An error exists in the handling of "smb:" and "sftp:" URI schemes on Linux systems with gnome-vfs support. This can be exploited to read any file owned by the target user via a specially crafted page on the same server. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has write access to a mutually accessible location on the target server and the user is tricked into loading the malicious page.
			7) An unspecified error in the handling of "XPCNativeWrappers" can lead to execution of arbitrary Javascript code with the user's privileges via subsequent access by the browser chrome (e.g. when a user right-clicks to open a context menu).</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>305</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>firefox</package>
		<vulnerable>2.0.0.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.0.0.8-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2235
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2513</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-1095
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-2292
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4841
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5334
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5337
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5338
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5339
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5340
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3511</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities and a weakness have been reported in Mozilla Firefox, which can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information, conduct phishing attacks, manipulate certain data, and potentially compromise a user's system.
			1) Various errors in the browser engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption.
			2) Various errors in the Javascript engine can be exploited to cause a memory corruption. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities may allow execution of arbitrary code.
			3) An error in the handling of onUnload events can be exploited to read and manipulate the document's location of new pages.
			4) Input passed to the user ID when making an HTTP request using Digest Authentication is not properly sanitised before being used in a request. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTTP headers into a user's request when a proxy is used.
			5) An error when displaying web pages written in the XUL markup language can be exploited to hide the window's title bar and facilitate phishing attacks.
			6) An error exists in the handling of "smb:" and "sftp:" URI schemes on Linux systems with gnome-vfs support. This can be exploited to read any file owned by the target user via a specially crafted page on the same server. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has write access to a mutually accessible location on the target server and the user is tricked into loading the malicious page.
			7) An unspecified error in the handling of "XPCNativeWrappers" can lead to execution of arbitrary Javascript code with the user's privileges via subsequent access by the browser chrome (e.g. when a user right-clicks to open a context menu).
			Furthermore a weakness has been discovered in Firefox, which potentially can be exploited by malicious people to disclose sensitive information.
			The weakness is caused due to a design error within the focus handling of form fields and can potentially be exploited by changing the focus from a "textarea" field to a "file upload" form field via the "OnKeyDown" event.
			Successful exploitation allows an arbitrary file on the user's system to be uploaded to a malicious web site, but requires that the user is tricked into typing the file name into a "textarea" input form.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>304</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>drupal</package>
		<vulnerable>5.2-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>5.2-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2507</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5595
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5596
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5597
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5593
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5594</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and bypass certain security restrictions, and by malicious users to conduct HTTP response splitting attacks.
			1) Input passed to unspecified parameters is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to insert arbitrary HTTP headers, which is included in a response sent to the user. This allows arbitrary HTML and script code to be executed in a user's browser session in context of an affected site. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires valid user credentials.
			2) The Upload module includes the ".html" file extension in its default whitelist for file uploads. This can be exploited to upload arbitrary HTML files and enticing users to visit them, thereby executing arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.
			3) The hook_components API operation does not pass the publication status. This makes it possible for modules including Organic groups and Subscriptions to send e-mail messages containing unpublished comments.
			Furthermore vulnerabilities have been reported in Drupal, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site request forgery attacks and to compromise a vulnerable system.
			1) Input passed to unspecified parameters in install.php is not properly sanitised. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary code. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires that the configured SQL server is not reachable.
			2) A vulnerability is caused due to the application allowing users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any validity checks to verify the request. This can be exploited to delete users by enticing a logged-in administrator to visit a malicious site.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>303</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>opera</package>
		<vulnerable>9.23-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>9.24-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2502</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5540
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5541</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in Opera, where one vulnerability has an unknown impact and others can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and to compromise a user's system.
			1) Opera may launch external email or newsgroup clients incorrectly. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary commands by e.g. visiting a malicious website. Successful exploitation requires that the user has configured an external email or newsgroup client.
			2) An error when processing frames from different websites can be exploited to bypass the same-origin policy. This allows to overwrite functions of those frames and to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of other sites.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>302</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>hplip</package>
		<vulnerable>2.7.7-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.7.7-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2496</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5208</cve>
		<desc>Kees Cook has reported a vulnerability in HPLIP, which can be exploited by malicious, local users to gain escalated privileges.
			The vulnerability is caused due to the hpssd daemon not properly sanitising certain input before using it to invoke sendmail using the "popen3()" method. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary commands with escalated privileges (e.g. "root") by sending specially crafted requests to the hpssd daemon.
			NOTE: Depending upon the configuration of hpssd, this may also be remotely exploitable.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>301</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>madwifi</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.3.2-4</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.3.3-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2495</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5448</cve>
		<desc>Clemens Kolbitsch and Sylvester Keil have reported a vulnerability in MadWifi, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error in the processing of beacon frames. This can be exploited via a specially crafted beacon frame with an overly large "length" value (greater than 15) in the extended supported rates element ("xrates").
			Successful exploitation causes the driver to exit and results in a kernel panic.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>300</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>phpmyadmin</package>
		<vulnerable>2.11.1-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>2.11.1.2-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2489
			http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2503</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5386</cve>
		<desc>Omer Singer has reported two vulnerabilities in phpMyAdmin, which can be exploited by malicious people to conduct cross-site scripting attacks.
			1) Input passed via the URL is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site. Successful exploitation requires that the user is running a browser that has not URL-encoded the request (e.g. Internet Explorer 6).
			2) Input passed in the URL to server_status.php is not properly sanitised before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site. Successful exploitation requires that the target user has valid user credentials. NOTE: Some other potential cross-site scripting problems have also been fixed by the vendor.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>299</id>
		<date>2007-10-23</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>openssl</package>
		<vulnerable>0.9.8-9</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>0.9.8-10sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2488</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4995</cve>
		<desc>Andy Polyakov has reported a vulnerability in OpenSSL, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service) and potentially compromise a vulnerable system.
			The vulnerability is caused due to an unspecified error within the DTLS implementation. Successful exploitation may allow the execution of arbitrary code.
			Note: Reportedly, this vulnerability affects only clients and servers explicitly using DTLS.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>298</id>
		<date>2007-10-19</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>pwlib</package>
		<vulnerable>1.10.10-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.10.10-2sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2491</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-4897</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been discovered in PWLib, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an error within the "PString::vsprintf()" method in src/ptlib/common/contain.cxx. This can be exploited to cause a memory corruption by e.g. tricking an application using the library to use this function with a string longer than 1000 bytes.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>297</id>
		<date>2007-10-19</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>wesnoth</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.6-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.6-2terminus1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2486</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-3917</cve>
		<desc>A vulnerability has been reported in Wesnoth, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			The vulnerability is caused due to an unspecified error in the processing of UTF-8 strings within the multiplayer engine . This can be exploited by malicious clients to crash a vulnerable Wesnoth client.</desc>
	</fsa>
	<fsa>
		<id>296</id>
		<date>2007-10-19</date>
		<author>voroskoi</author>
		<package>libpng</package>
		<vulnerable>1.2.20-1</vulnerable>
		<unaffected>1.2.22-1sayshell1</unaffected>
		<bts>http://bugs.frugalware.org/task/2475</bts>
		<cve>http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5267
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5266
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5268
			http://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2007-5269</cve>
		<desc>Some vulnerabilities have been reported in libpng, which can be exploited by malicious people to cause a DoS (Denial of Service).
			1) Certain errors within libpng, including a logical NOT instead of a bitwise NOT in pngtrtran.c, an error in the 16bit cheap transparency extension, and an incorrect use of sizeof() may be exploited to crash an application using the library.
			2) Various out-of-bounds read errors exist within the functions "png_handle_pCAL()", "png_handle_sCAL()", "png_push_read_tEXt()", "png_handle_iTXt()", and "png_handle_ztXt()", which may be exploited by exploited to crash an application using the library.
			3) The vulnerability is caused due to an off-by-one error within the ICC profile chunk handling, which potentially can be exploited to crash an application using the library.</desc>
	</fsa>
</fsas>
